Using Xiaoboda to enhance citizens' digital resilience through tools and communities
Xiaoboda を使用してツールとコミュニティを通じて国民のデジタル レジリエンスを強化する
It is a great honor to have this opportunity to make an opening here today
本日はここにオープニングを飾る機会をいただき大変光栄です
Then I remember that in the planning of our lecture topics in the first two sessions
その後、最初の 2 つのセッションでの講義のトピックを計画する際に、次のことを思い出しました。
We compare the so-called digital resilience issue from the national level
いわゆるデジタルレジリエンス問題を国家レベルで比較します
Let's talk about it, I remember we talked about
それについて話しましょう、私たちが話したことを覚えています
Probably a resilience in terms of infrastructure, communications infrastructure
おそらくインフラストラクチャ、通信インフラストラクチャの回復力
how to do it
どうやってするの
So when we talk about oceans, when we talk about satellites, when we talk about war
ですから、私たちが海洋について話すとき、衛星について話すとき、戦争について話すとき
What are the alternatives and what has the government done to prepare?
代替案は何ですか?政府はその準備のために何をしましたか?
Then I think we will also talk about digital resilience in today's session
それでは、今日のセッションではデジタル レジリエンスについてもお話したいと思います
But we landed today we landed today
でも今日着陸した今日着陸した
So what we're going to discuss today is
それで、今日私たちが議論することは、
Every citizen at the time of this possible disaster
この起こり得る災害の際にすべての国民が
or the moment when there may be a war situation in the future
または将来戦争状態になるかもしれない瞬間
whether before, during or after
前でも最中でも後でも
what can we do
私たちは何ができる
To build a digital resilience that belongs to this citizen
この国民に属するデジタル レジリエンスを構築する
Jiang Tang is also very honored for this event
Jiang Tangもこのイベントをとても光栄に思います
We have invited the Digital Diplomacy Association to be our partner in this
私たちはデジタル外交協会をこの活動のパートナーとして招待しました。
Then I think the Digital Diplomacy Association has been
それから、デジタル外交協会は、
They're in the middle of this war in Ukraine
彼らはウクライナで戦争の真っ只中にいる
They also made quite a bit of an observation related to this
彼らはまた、これに関連するかなりの観察を行いました
Then I want to cheer up and wait for it to be included in his sharing.
それから私は元気を出して、それが彼の共有に含まれるのを待ちたいと思います。
Let me give you a more detailed introduction
さらに詳しくご紹介させていただきます
Well I think we're happy with this today
まあ、今日はこれで満足だと思います
Today we invite this very grassroots group
今日私たちはこの草の根グループを招待します
whether citizen group media
市民団体メディアかどうか
Or a representative of this tech community or startup
または、この技術コミュニティまたはスタートアップの代表者
Come to share with you such a topic
このような話題を共有しに来てください
Then I think I will first introduce our host for this session
それでは、最初にこのセッションのホストを紹介したいと思います
Then for this session we invited this crap Red National Army Chief Operating Officer
そしてこのセッションには、このくだらない赤国軍最高執行責任者を招待しました
The chief operating officer of the National Army used to be the editor-in-chief of the shit
国軍の最高執行責任者はかつてクソ雑誌の編集長だった
And then there's this Citizens Watch, director of policy at the Congressional Coalition
そして、このシチズンズ・ウォッチ、議会連合の政策部長です。
Then he also participated in editing this shit
それから彼はこのたわごとの編集にも参加しました
The Civic Action Guide published a while ago
少し前に発行された市民活動ガイド
I also make a small recommendation here
ここでもちょっとしたお勧めをします
In fact, it is really worth buying the basics
実際、基本を買う価値はあります
By the way, buy more and give them to relatives and friends
ちなみに、もっと買って親戚や友達に贈ってください
I think I'll put the time behind
時間を後回しにしようと思う
Give it to our military operations chief
それを軍事作戦責任者に渡してください
The chief operating officer will leave it to you
最高執行責任者があなたにお任せします
Thanks
ありがとう
Thank you for the introduction
紹介してくれたホストさん、ありがとう
and today's guests
そして今日のゲスト
There are also friends from the media participating
メディア関係者の友人も参加しています
I didn't think the host would follow the opening
司会者がオープニングに従うとは思わなかった
help us lose first
私たちが最初に負けるのを手伝ってください
but this is embarrassing
でもこれは恥ずかしい
But I think this is a private unit
でもここはプライベートユニットだと思う
Different from government departments
政府機関との違い
I think it's a
だと思います
Just mentioned a good opening
良いオープニングについて言及しました
Like today, I also invited many friends from non-governmental organizations
今日と同様に、私も非政府組織から多くの友人を招待しました
I think we do things differently
私たちは物事のやり方が違うと思う
but to some extent
しかしある程度は
we just see the same problem
同じ問題が見えているだけです
some things are
いくつかのことは
We feel like someone should do it
私たちは誰かがやるべきだと感じています
but no one does
でも誰もやらない
we might feel like saying
と言いたくなるかもしれません
this thing maybe
これはもしかしたら
big business to do
やるべき大きなビジネス
Maybe the government department will do
たぶん政府部門がやってくれるだろう
maybe some people are going to come out and do it
もしかしたら何人かが出てきてそれをやろうとしているかもしれない
But we may find ourselves saying
しかし、私たちは自分自身がこう言っていることに気づくかもしれません
Eh, it seems that when no one comes out to do it
えー、誰も出てこない時はそうなるみたいです
we need to know
私たちは知る必要がある
well you're the one who doesn't
まあ、あなたはそうしない人です
we're going to act like no one
私たちは誰でもないように振る舞うつもりです
do this first
最初にこれをしてください
Start small
小さく始めてください
After letting other government departments see
他の省庁に見てもらった上で
Willingness is to use more resources to invest
より多くのリソースを投資に活用する意欲がある
make this thing better
これをより良くする
Then of course we will talk about this topic today
もちろん今日はこのテーマについて話します
I think it's still going back to saying something like
まだ次のようなことを言うことに戻っていると思います
Ukrainian city of Russia
ロシアのウクライナの都市
Ukraine has been more than a year
ウクライナは1年以上経ちました
That doesn't look like it's going to stop yet.
それはまだ止まりそうにありません。
Many people will compare
比べてしまう人も多いでしょう
Some people say that Taiwan and Ukraine
台湾とウクライナだと言う人もいる
Hey, Taiwan looks a lot like Ukraine
おい、台湾はウクライナによく似ている
But some people say that Taiwan is very different from Ukraine
しかし、台湾はウクライナとは大きく異なるという人もいます。
Both are right, there are differences
どちらも正しい、違いはある
how to say
どのように言って
In fact, we see Ukraine
実際、私たちはウクライナを見ています
this is able to block
これはブロックできる
This Russian Wu Qing
このロシアの呉清
A very important key is to
非常に重要な鍵となるのは、
It is the power of their democratization
それは彼らの民主化の力です
able to play out
プレイアウトできる
Not just the strength of the army
軍隊の強さだけではない
Their democrat morale has improved enough
彼らの民主主義の士気は十分に向上した
To Party Under Russia's Invasion
党の下でのロシアの侵略
This reminds us of one thing
これは私たちに一つのことを思い出させます
That is to say, we used to lie on the grass and make some
つまり、私たちは草の上に寝転んで何かを作っていました。
Civilian interviews, when it comes to defense-related topics
防衛関連の話題に関する民間人インタビュー
A scholar put forward a very important concept
学者が非常に重要な概念を提唱しました
I think this is a
これは
Today we're going to be here on this topic
今日はこのテーマについてお話します
a very important reason
非常に重要な理由
He said war, defense of Taiwan
彼は戦争だ、台湾の防衛だと言いました
this matter is too important
この問題はあまりにも重要です
so that what not to just give
与えてはいけないものを
Ministry of Defense
防衛省
what does this story tell us
この物語は私たちに何を伝えますか
Today's government departments may generally think of saying
今日、政府部門では一般的に次のように考えるかもしれません。
Who will be responsible if there is a war
戦争になったら誰が責任を取るのか
The Ministry of Defense, the barracks are going to be responsible
防衛省、兵舎が責任を持つことになる
Actually not only, not only the Ministry of Defense
実はそれだけじゃない、防衛省だけじゃない
departments of government like
政府の各部門のような
This chef is very
このシェフはとても
In fact, many government agencies are responsible for
実際、多くの政府機関が責任を負っています。
Protection of Critical Records Facilities
重要な記録施設の保護
Maybe the Ministry of Health and Welfare, the Ministry of Transportation, the Ministry of the Interior, etc.
厚生省、運輸省、内務省などでしょうか。
to join the government
政府に参加する
overall defense
全体的な防御力
Is it the government's responsibility?
それは政府の責任ですか？
Not really
あまり
Folks are also important
庶民も大事だよ
How civil groups and individuals
市民団体や個人がどのように
The power of the grassroots
草の根の力
Improve the defense of Taiwan as a whole
台湾全体の防衛を強化する
very dangerous
すごく危ない
This is how to keep
こうやって飼うんだ
A key to field aggression
フィールドアグレッシブの鍵
and we also know that
そして私たちもそれを知っています
People often say that masters are among the people
名人は人の中にあるとよく言われます
Does it mean that the government department
政府部門ということですか？
sometimes unwilling to do things
時々物事をしたくない
Or they are lazy
それとも怠け者なのか
or something
か何か
Sometimes some ideas belong to government departments
一部のアイデアは政府部門に属する場合があります
did not think of
考えなかった
Our folk role is to test
私たちの民の役割はテストすることです
give them something different
彼らに何か違うものを与えてください
let them know say
彼らに言ってもらいましょう
It turns out that some problems can be solved like this
いくつかの問題はこのように解決できることがわかりました
So today of course I am today
だから今日ももちろん私は今日です
responsible for hosting
ホスティングを担当する
but it doesn't mean
しかしそれは意味がありません
This is the most powerful
これが一番強力です
I think the next few guests
次の数人のゲストは
Actually a very good one
実際、とても良いものです
speakers they are many good
スピーカーは良いものがたくさんあります
I can share with you today
今日は皆さんと共有できます
How to Citizenship Tech
シティズンシップテックのやり方
can be used in this corner of our defense of Taiwan
台湾防衛のこの一角で使用できる
this plays an important role
これは重要な役割を果たします
Then let me briefly introduce a few speakers
それでは、いくつかの講演者を簡単にご紹介します
that one is the president of the country
あの人はその国の大統領です
Of course, everyone should go through
もちろん、誰もが通過する必要があります
Sugui Diplomatic Association
杉井外交協会
In fact, in recent years
実は近年、
in online communities
オンラインコミュニティで
Helped Taiwan to do a lot of things
台湾に多くのことを手伝ってもらいました
let more people know
もっと多くの人に知ってもらいましょう
Taiwan's Dilemma Internationally
国際的な台湾のジレンマ
and then we
そして私たちは
What can we do to everyone in the international community
国際社会の皆さんに私たちができること
It is Taiwan Can Help Taiwan Is Helping
台湾は助けられる 台湾は助けられる
Give full play to the visibility of everyone in Taiwan and in the world
台湾だけでなく世界中の人々の注目を集めるために最大限の効果を発揮する
Then there is our founder Xu Wulong
次に、創業者の徐武龍です。
It’s also called Haba in reverse, right?
逆にハバとも言いますよね？
It's that he's actually been a citizen tech all along.
それは、彼が実際にはずっと市民技術者であったということです。
We all call it through some hikes
私たちは皆、ハイキングを通じてそれを呼びます
Some technology and engineering methods allow everyone to participate in politics
一部のテクノロジーやエンジニアリング手法により、誰もが政治に参加できるようになります
like if i'm not mistaken
私が間違っていないかのように
There was an important one before
この前に大事な事があった
and also an interesting project
そしてまた興味深いプロジェクト
air box
エアボックス
How to let everyone use the power of the people
国民の力をみんなにどうやって活用してもらうか
to let everyone know
みんなに知らせるために
How is the air quality in all parts of Taiwan?
台湾各地の空気の質はどうですか?
This is a grassroots force from the bottom up
これは下からの草の根の力です
You can also urge the government to make some policy changes
政府に政策変更を促すこともできます
Then come to the end, of course he still has this director Cai Wencheng Q-SURGE
それで最後に来ます、もちろん彼はまだこの監督を持っています 蔡文成 Q-SURGE
I think this thing does not matter whether it is a figure in the industry or a politician
これは業界人でも政治家でも関係ないと思う
know the tool very well.
ツールをよく知っています。
We can use this Q-SURGE to understand
この Q-SURGE を使用すると、
What's going on in the community right now?
今コミュニティで何が起こっているのでしょうか？
This matter may not be used anymore
この件はもう使用できないかもしれません
in business or in our political situation
ビジネスや政治情勢において
this mastery of entertainment
このエンターテイメントの熟練
Another very important thing is
もう一つ非常に重要なことは、
In addition to shooting and setting up guns in modern warfare
現代戦争における銃の射撃と設置に加えて
community fake news
コミュニティのフェイクニュース
can also play an important role
重要な役割を果たすこともできます
i want to wait maybe
たぶん待ちたい
The director will also share with us
監督も教えてくれますよ
What kind of help can Q-Sage provide here?
Q-Sage はここでどのような支援を提供できますか?
then we first we first
それから私たちが最初に私たちが最初に
Let's first ask Guo Jiayou, the wise man, to share with us, shall we?
まずは賢者の郭嘉佑さんに教えてもらってみましょうか？
Thanks
ありがとう
Hello everyone, distinguished guests, friends online, hello everyone
皆様、ご来賓の皆様、オンラインの友人の皆様、こんにちは。
I am Guo Jiayou, the chairman of Taiwan Digital Diplomacy Association
私は台湾デジタル外交協会会長の郭嘉佑です。
Then today's words are actually
では今日の言葉は実は
I want to use some little stories from Ukraine
ウクライナの小さな物語をいくつか使いたいと思います
Let me share with you that in the war between Ukraine and Russia
ウクライナとロシアの間の戦争でのことを共有しましょう
What are they doing for their fame?
彼らは名声のために何をしているのでしょうか？
Because you may have seen news about Ukraine last year
昨年のウクライナに関するニュースを見たことがあるかもしれないから
There was a lot of discussion last year that
昨年もいろいろ議論がありましたが、
I'm an ordinary person, what kind of things can I do?
私は一般人ですが、どんなことができるでしょうか？
Because what we usually use is on social media
私たちが普段使っているのはソーシャルメディアだから
I might share with you what I ate today.
今日食べたものをシェアするかもしれません。
Or what news did you see today?
あるいは今日どんなニュースを見ましたか？
Is there any way for something like this to exert any influence?
このようなことが何らかの影響を与える方法はあるのでしょうか？
We will spend 15 minutes today to briefly discuss with you
今日は 15 分間、簡単にお話しします。
Then let me briefly introduce why our association started
それでは、当協会が発足した経緯を簡単にご紹介させていただきます
The project focuses on the defense of the network
このプロジェクトはネットワークの防御に焦点を当てています
First of all, it means that last year we actually
まず第一に、それは昨年、実際に私たちが
So the Diplomatic Council has always been on social media
つまり、外交評議会は常にソーシャルメディア上にありました
promoting Taiwan and other countries
台湾やその他の国を宣伝する
partnership, so we usually hang on the Internet naturally
パートナーシップなので、普段は自然にインターネットにアクセスしています
It's almost like this all day to see what's happening on the Internet abroad
海外のインターネットで何が起こっているかを見ると、ほぼ一日中このような感じです
Last year, we observed on the Internet that, in fact, Ukrainian
昨年、私たちはインターネット上で、実際にはウクライナ人が
the masses they are very
彼らはとても大衆です
doing a lot spontaneously
自発的にたくさんのことをする
A lot of them will set up their own websites, information websites
彼らの多くは自分のウェブサイトや情報ウェブサイトを立ち上げるでしょう
In other words, they will initiate some
言い換えれば、彼らはいくつかのことを始めるだろう
Some common actions on the Internet
インターネット上での一般的なアクション
Then we think these things are actually worthy of Taiwan’s reference.
そして、これらのことは実際に台湾にとって参考に値するものであると考えます。
Because he needs the content of these networks
彼はこれらのネットワークのコンテンツを必要としているため、
Vision is planned or vision is
ビジョンは計画されているか、ビジョンは
Understand, it's a bit like K-Study, let's start with
わかります、これは K-Study に似ています。まず始めましょう。
Use Ukraine as a mirror, let’s see it first
ウクライナを鏡として、まずは見てみましょう
What kind of cases have they done? In the future, when Taiwan prepares for this, compare
彼らはどのような事例を行ったのでしょうか? 将来、台湾がこのような準備をするとき、比較してください。
It won't be so busy, so
そんなに忙しくはならないので、
exist
存在
In the content we focus on, in fact
私たちが注力しているコンテンツでは、実は
We are not focusing on fake news
私たちはフェイクニュースには焦点を当てていません
Because of false information, many units in Taiwan are actually doing it
誤った情報のせいで、台湾の多くの部隊が実際にそれを行っている
We are more focused on content production
私たちはコンテンツ制作にさらに重点を置いています
how to go
どうやって行くか
After identifying fake news
フェイクニュースを特定した後
The part behind you is going
あなたの後ろの部分が進んでいます
to generate from content
コンテンツから生成する
to fight disinformation
偽情報と戦うために
Let's say there's probably no fake news out there.
おそらくフェイクニュースは存在しないとしましょう。
You also have to keep making
あなたも作り続けなければなりません
social content on the web
ウェブ上のソーシャル コンテンツ
only you can make
あなただけが作ることができます
People from other countries continue to discuss
他国の人々が議論を続けている
your situation
あなたの状況
So today's sharing will be more focused on
したがって、今日の共有は次の点に重点を置きます。
It's what's on the internet
それはインターネット上にあるものです
How to make it
作り方
good
良い
Civic willfulness is this
市民の故意とはこれです
Everyone is talking about
みんなが話しているのは
what kind of action
どのような行動ですか
Can be strengthened
強化可能
For example, Taiwan's Internet
例えば台湾のインターネット
Citizen willfulness
市民の故意
To me, it's civic willfulness
私にとって、それは市民の故意です
it's a lot of
たくさんあるよ
A thing connected by nodes
ノードでつながったもの
just say everyone
みんな言ってください
Everyone is a channel for information dissemination
誰もが情報発信のチャンネルになる
You have your own social platform
あなたは独自のソーシャルプラットフォームを持っています
You have a network of people around you
あなたの周りには人々のネットワークがあります
everyone is one
誰もが一つです
node of information dissemination
情報発信の結節点
Then when everyone knows how to do this
そして誰もがこれを行う方法を知ったとき
When information is disseminated, in fact, many of us
実際、情報が広められると、私たちの多くは
When many dots are connected, he will become a
たくさんの点が繋がると、彼は
a net
一個網
The more sticky this net is, the more self-willed citizens will be
この網が粘着的であればあるほど、より利己的な国民が増える
stronger
より強く
That
それか
if we are here we can
私たちがここにいるなら、それができます
Let me share with you about last year
昨年のことをお話しさせてください
How the Digital Diplomacy Association might be involved in this online community in Ukraine
デジタル外交協会がウクライナのこのオンライン コミュニティにどのように関与する可能性があるか
Let's say there was a meme in Ukraine last year and he was full
去年ウクライナでミームがあったとして、彼は満腹だったとしましょう。
The one full of red is called a headache map, that's what they say
赤でいっぱいのものは頭痛マップと呼ばれるものです、そう言うのです
My head hurts when I live next to Russia
ロシアの隣に住んでいると頭が痛くなる
then we'll be
それなら私たちはそうなります
To do one is to live in
何かをすることは、そこに住むことだ
China's side headache also hurts. This meme got about 230,000 likes on the Internet.
中国の脇腹頭痛も痛い このミームはインターネット上で約23万件の「いいね！」を獲得した。
That is, everyone started to discuss the situation of Taiwan and the situation of Ukraine.
つまり、台湾の状況とウクライナの状況について皆が議論し始めたのです。
is it similar
似ていますか
then we are
それなら私たちは
Beyond the topic of Ukraine
ウクライナの話題を超えて
In addition to the topic of Ukraine, there are actually
ウクライナの話題に加えて、実は、
have done some
いくつかやった
did some political cartoons
いくつかの政治漫画を描きました
We'll do political cartoons in different languages
政治漫画をさまざまな言語で制作します
For example, Lai Qingde visited Honduras before
たとえば、頼清徳氏は以前ホンジュラスを訪問しました。
At that time, Hongdullas was still Taiwan's helper, but now it is not.
当時、ホンドゥラスはまだ台湾の助っ人だったが、今はそうではない。
In the past, when he was visiting
以前、彼が訪れたとき、
We made him a political cartoon
私たちは彼を政治漫画にしました
So Vice President Lai Qingde and the Vice President of the United States
頼清徳副総統と米国副大統領
Put it with the president of Red Durres
レッド・デュレスの社長に言ってください
In this political cartoon they eat street food in Red Durran together
この政治漫画では、彼らはレッド デュランで屋台の食べ物を一緒に食べます
So we used this political cartoon to send the first message on the Internet saying
そこで私たちはこの政治漫画を利用して、インターネット上に次のような最初のメッセージを送りました。
It means being good friends with Taiwan
それは台湾と良い友達になることを意味します
It's like being good friends with the United States
アメリカと仲が良いようなものです
This is the way to spread the word to the people of Central and South America
これが中南米の人々に情報を広める方法です
Those private pictures
それらのプライベート写真
Then we'll give it back to the public in the comments
その後、コメントで一般公開します
will collect again
また集めます
Then it will be made into international news
そうしたら国際ニュースになるよ
It is to talk more about Taiwan's positive image abroad
台湾のポジティブなイメージを海外にもっと伝えることです
that or sometimes
それか時々
Sometimes when some countries break off diplomatic relations with Taiwan
時々、一部の国が台湾と国交を断絶することがあります。
We'll also start some
私たちもいくつか始めます
Actions on the Internet. For example, Solomon broke off diplomatic relations with Taiwan in 2019.
インターネット上のアクション たとえば、ソロモンは 2019 年に台湾との国交を断絶しました。
We have initiated some
いくつか始めました
A series of posts to talk about, although the relationship is broken
関係は壊れているが、話題になる一連の投稿
But the people of Taiwan and the people of Solomon can still be good friends
しかし、台湾の人々とソロモンの人々は今でも良い友達でいられる
It also caused a lot of repercussions in the local area.
地元でも大きな反響を呼びました。
So we're doing digital diplomacy and we'll see that
ですから私たちはデジタル外交を行っています、そしてそれが分かるでしょう
In fact, digital diplomacy is a long-term
実際、デジタル外交は長期にわたるものです。
Create community content and then influence it in other countries' societies
コミュニティ コンテンツを作成し、他の国の社会に影響を与える
The public opinion of the masses in other countries, or in other words, to influence the opinions of other countries
他国の大衆の世論、つまり他国の意見に影響を与えること
It is up to the people of other countries to influence the decision-making of the local government
地方自治体の意思決定に影響を与えるのは他国の人々次第です
So their digital diplomacy is actually in the current
つまり、彼らのデジタル外交は実際に現在行われているのです
In the online world, it is actually a relatively easy to measure
オンラインの世界では、実際には比較的簡単に測定できます。
It has a way to measure its effectiveness and the number of people it reaches
その効果とそれが届く人の数を測定する方法がある
an action like this
このようなアクション
So let's go back to last year, let's turn the time forward to last year
それで、去年に戻りましょう、時間を昨年に戻しましょう
February 24th of last year was when Russia began its invasion of Ukraine
昨年の2月24日はロシアがウクライナへの侵攻を開始した日だった
What happened to Ukraine's Internet
ウクライナのインターネットに何が起こったのか
You can see that the war has not yet started, when it started to be very intense
戦争はまだ始まっておらず、非常に激しくなり始めたことがわかります。
Here we summarize a little
ここで少しまとめます
Three days before the Ukrainian war started their
ウクライナ戦争が始まる3日前に、
Some posts by government officials on Twitter
政府関係者によるツイッターへの投稿の一部
you can see that in fact
実際にそれがわかります
exist
存在
72 hours into the war they say their
戦争開始から72時間経って彼らはこう言う
The digital minister is a bit like their digital department
デジタル大臣はデジタル部門に似ています
So I started to appeal to companies all over the world
そこで私は世界中の企業に訴え始めました
stop providing services to russia because they are doing illegal intrusion
ロシアが不法侵入を行っているため、ロシアへのサービス提供を停止する
That is to say their Prime Minister will start to
つまり、彼らの首相は、
shout out to the world
世界に向かって叫ぶ
then in
それから
In these
これらの中で
In addition to the Ukrainian government’s own posts on the Internet, you can also see various companies
インターネット上ではウクライナ政府自身の投稿に加えて、さまざまな企業の投稿も見ることができます
They also tweet
彼らもツイートしてるよ
Or through Facebook or various social platforms they start responding
または、Facebook やさまざまなソーシャル プラットフォームを通じて反応を開始します。
Views on the Ukraine War
ウクライナ戦争に関する見解
So machine warfare is actually a hybrid type of warfare.
したがって、機械戦争は実際にはハイブリッド型の戦争です。
it's not just in physical wars
それは物理的な戦争だけではない
This kind of mutual speech on the Internet
インターネット上でのこのような相互発言
In fact, it will also affect the development of the entire war situation.
実際、それは戦局全体の展開にも影響を与えるだろう。
Here even companies from various countries have begun to condemn Russia
ここにきて各国の企業もロシアを非難し始めている
Then publish it on the Internet like this
次に、このようにインターネット上に公開します
Well, Ukraine actually has a lot of government apps
そうですね、ウクライナには実際に政府のアプリがたくさんあります
Then there are also developed
それから、開発されたものもあります
For example, this missing par
たとえば、この欠けているパー
It's a shorthand in Telegram
テレグラムの略称です
It is to allow the public to go to the
一般人が行けるようにするためです
Repay in this Telegram trap
このテレグラムの罠で返済してください
A first-hand view of a situation where they are located
それらが置かれている状況を直接見る
This is what they digitally don't build
これは彼らがデジタルで構築しないものです
Then I was in February last February
それから私は去年の2月に
I have private message my Ukrainian friend
ウクライナ人の友人にプライベートメッセージを送っています
I asked him how are you doing now?
私は彼に今はどうしているのかと尋ねました。
so you are now in ukraine
それであなたは今ウクライナにいます
Is there anything I need help with?
何か手助けが必要なことはありますか?
My Ukrainian friend replied
ウクライナ人の友人が返信しました
In fact, he thinks that as long as the atrocities of Russia can be spread
実際、彼はロシアの残虐行為が広まる限りはそう考えている
Letting more people know is the biggest help for them
より多くの人に知ってもらうことが彼らにとって最大の助けとなる
Because they actually
なぜなら彼らは実際に
It is difficult for us to contact them directly
直接ご連絡することが難しいため、
but we have internet
しかし、私たちにはインターネットがあります
when we have internet
インターネットがあるとき
We can help our friends in Ukraine
私たちはウクライナの友人たちを助けることができます
spread this information
この情報を広める
What can you do after it spreads out?
蔓延した後は何ができるのでしょうか？
Because more and more people will discuss
議論する人が増えるから
will push the governments of various countries to start formalizing this issue
さまざまな国の政府にこの問題を公式化するよう促すだろう
The governments of various countries will impose sanctions on Russia
各国政府がロシアに制裁を発動
the community actually
実際にコミュニティ
The community as a small brother's big combat tool
小さな兄弟の大きな戦闘ツールとしてのコミュニティ
Then we will share with you today
それでは今日は皆さんとシェアさせていただきます
In other words, it is used by communities between Taiwan and Ukraine
つまり、台湾とウクライナの間のコミュニティで使用されています。
What is the difference between us
私たちの違いは何ですか
or did something different
あるいは何か違うことをした
good
良い
the whole world
全世界
What the whole world does with the community is actually what he basically wants
全世界がコミュニティに対して行っていることは、実は彼が基本的に望んでいることなのです
Do your best to help Ukraine spread the message
ウクライナのメッセージを広めるために最善を尽くしてください
Because in war, there is one very important thing
戦争においてはとても大切なことが一つあるからです
is to build a value alliance
価値あるアライアンスを構築することです
Then you have to go to all the Internet to discuss this matter
この問題を議論するにはインターネット全体にアクセスする必要があります
pull to the same side as you feel saying
あなたが言うのと同じ側に引っ張ってください
He agrees with you in this war
彼はこの戦争であなたに同意します
legitimacy and morality, so the community can spread
正当性と道徳性を備え、コミュニティが広がることができる
your values ​​spread your values ​​and go
あなたの価値観があなたの価値観を広げて行きます
A platform to influence public opinion
世論に影響を与えるプラットフォーム
For example, the previous icon has to be
たとえば、前のアイコンは次のようにする必要があります。
The domain of the former Soviet Union was removed, and this is also in
旧ソ連のネットワークドメインが削除され、これも
One made after some discussions on the Internet
ネット上で議論を重ねて作ったもの
A decision looks like this or in
決定は次のようになります。
There are many politicians in Ukraine and they will go
ウクライナには政治家がたくさんいるし、彼らは去っていくだろう
will go for a specific specific event to happen
特定の特定のイベントが起こるために行きます
You can see that in these
これらを見ればそれがわかります
That is, in the speeches of politicians, they are actually targeting
つまり、政治家の演説では、実際に次のことをターゲットにしているのです。
They are actually targeting that, that is what international organizations are doing.
彼らは実際にそれをターゲットにしており、それが国際機関が行っていることです。
International organizations are making a call
国際機関が呼びかけを行っている
can help me next page thanks
次のページを手伝ってください、ありがとう
So here’s what you can say to him on social media
ソーシャルメディアで彼に言えることは次のとおりです
For example, if there are people from Ukraine, they will contact Beckham
たとえば、ウクライナ出身の人がいたら、ベッカムに連絡します。
Then they borrowed Beckham's IG
それから彼らはベッカムのIGを借りました
Then convey the battle situation in the Ukrainian hospital
続いてウクライナの病院での戦闘状況を伝える
Because Beckham has a lot of traffic
ベッカムは交通量が多いので
It is said that this post has been seen by 4 million people
この投稿は400万人が閲覧したそうです
So they use different social platforms
したがって、彼らは異なるソーシャルプラットフォームを使用しています
Or to work with different hospital leaders
または、さまざまな病院のリーダーと協力することもできます
Then go to convey the content they have done and find the right channel to spread it out
次に、彼らが行ったコンテンツを伝えに行き、それを広めるための適切なチャネルを見つけます。
ok help me next page thanks
わかりました、次のページを手伝ってください、ありがとう
So what did Ukraine do with the community?
それでは、ウクライナはコミュニティに対して何をしたのでしょうか?
In fact, they are mainly in Ukraine to maintain the popularity of a community
実際、彼らはコミュニティの人気を維持するために主にウクライナにいます。
Because their worst fear is that the world won't talk about them
なぜなら、彼らの最大の恐怖は、世界が自分たちのことについて話してくれなくなることだからです
when they are not discussed
議論されていないとき
They are a state of isolation
彼らは孤立状態にある
So Ukrainians use community
だからウクライナ人はコミュニティを利用する
The main thing they do is
彼らが主にやっているのは、
To maintain the enthusiasm of a community
コミュニティの熱意を維持するために
can you help me with the next one thanks
次のことを手伝ってもらえますか、ありがとう
Then their posts are actually
そして、彼らの投稿は実際には
You can see that they actually have
実際に持っていることがわかります。
Whether it's an emotional post
感情的な投稿であっても
or more informative posts
またはさらに有益な投稿
In fact, their request for publication will
実際、彼らの出版リクエストは、
The request for posting will be different
掲載依頼は異なります
sometimes they do memes
時々彼らはミームをやります
Will make meme maps or will make some
ミームマップを作成するか、いくつか作成する予定です
Comparison of photos before and after the war
戦前と戦後の写真の比較
that is a more emotional
それはより感情的なものです
It's a way of posting to arouse public awareness
世間の意識を高めるための投稿方法です
can help me next page
次のページを手伝ってください
There are more informational posts
さらに情報投稿があります
For example, the government will issue an announcement saying
たとえば、政府は次のような発表をします。
What are the methods of disinformation commonly used in Russia?
ロシアで一般的に使用されている偽情報の手法は何ですか?
Or where is the current supply spreading?
あるいは、現在の供給はどこに広がっているのでしょうか?
So there are some more informative posts
したがって、さらに有益な投稿がいくつかあります
In the communication of the community, it doesn’t matter whether it is
コミュニティのコミュニケーションにおいては、
informational or emotional hearing
情報的または感情的な聴覚
Both are needed
どちらも必要です
ok help me next page
はい、次のページを手伝ってください
Then I actually think that the Ukrainian government or the masses
それから私は実際にウクライナ政府または大衆が
They know how to express their needs through the community
彼らはコミュニティを通じて自分のニーズを表現する方法を知っています
Because you have to express your needs before you know how to say
なぜなら、言い方を知る前に自分のニーズを表現しなければならないからです
That is, the foreign government or the masses abroad
つまり、外国政府または海外の大衆
how to help
助ける方法
can help me next page
次のページを手伝ってください
And then to the one who just said that they're actually pretty good at going
そして、さっき言った人に、彼らは実際に行くのがかなり上手です
They are very good at cooperating with some overseas opinion leaders
彼らは海外のオピニオンリーダーと協力するのがとても上手です
For example Stephen King made a post for them
たとえば、スティーヴン・キングが彼らのために投稿をしました
This traffic is very high
このトラフィックは非常に多いです
ok help me next page
はい、次のページを手伝ってください
to that
それに対して
I just mentioned that the masses in Ukraine are very good at expressing their needs
ウクライナの大衆は自分たちのニーズを表現するのがとても上手だと先ほど言いました
Let's say there is a website called supportUkrain
supportUkrain という Web サイトがあるとします。
This website is actually open to foreigners
このウェブサイトは実は外国人にも開かれています
It's open to foreigners who want to support Ukraine
ウクライナを支援したい外国人も参加可能
It tells you that in fact you have a lot of ways
実際にはたくさんの方法があることがわかります
Can go to help people in Ukraine no matter what
何があってもウクライナの人々を助けに行くことができます
Say asylum or say you want to donate
亡命を言うか寄付したいと言う
Or you're going to be a volunteer and you're going to help them do translations
あるいは、あなたはボランティアになって彼らの翻訳を手伝うことになります。
or you want his
それとも彼が欲しいのですか
That is, you have to provide all kinds of organizational contacts, and he integrates all of them into
つまり、あらゆる種類の組織上の連絡先を提供する必要があり、彼はそれらすべてを統合します。
All in one website
オールインワンウェブサイト
That
それか
He even said he would
彼はそうすると言った
different
違う
post he will too
彼も投稿します
Put him all together, that is, his actions on the Internet, he also integrates him
彼をすべてまとめる、つまりインターネット上での彼の行動をまとめると、彼も彼を統合します
Before that, you may have heard that the Ukrainian people proposed to go to
その前に、ウクライナの人々がに行くことを提案したことを聞いたことがあるかもしれません
Under the Google Map of Russia
ロシアのGoogleマップの下で
Go leave a comment because the people of Russia didn't know their country was at war when they first attended
コメントを残してください。初めて参加したとき、ロシアの人々は自分の国が戦争中であることを知りませんでした。
so
それで
at that time
その時
Villagers in Ukraine launched a gambling operation called Go
ウクライナの村民が囲碁と呼ばれる賭博事業を開始
Google Map of Russia
ロシアのGoogleマップ
This left a message today, so he also put this online action on this website, which means saying
これは今日メッセージを残したので、彼はこのオンラインアクションもこのウェブサイトに掲載しました。つまり、次のように言います。
You just go to this site and you can
このサイトにアクセスするだけで、次のことが可能になります
click into various
いろいろクリックしてみる
Participate in some actions on the Internet
インターネット上の何らかのアクションに参加する
very convenient
とても便利
ok help me next page
はい、次のページを手伝ってください
Then in this case, we are still talking about Telegram
この場合、私たちはまだテレグラムについて話しています。
That is, everyone can see that Telegram is in the war between black and evil
つまり、テレグラムが黒人と悪との間の戦争に陥っていることは誰もが見ることができます。
actually played a very important role
実はとても重要な役割を果たしていた
Because in the war between black and evil, there are actually Telegram groups
なぜなら、黒人と悪の戦争では、実際にテレグラムグループが存在するからです。
He's growing at about the same rate as before.
彼は以前とほぼ同じ速度で成長しています。
Six times as much as when there was no war
戦争がなかったときの6倍
He has new groups every day
彼は毎日新しいグループを持っています
to provide new information
新しい情報を提供するため
would say he would have a different newsgroup
彼は別のニュースグループを持つだろうと言うだろう
I can exchange messages with you
あなたとメッセージを交換できます
There are also many foreigners
外国人の方もたくさんいらっしゃいます
They participate in these Telegrams
彼らはこれらの電報に参加しています
To provide assistance or to get first-hand information
支援を提供するため、または直接の情報を入手するため
In fact, the most important thing for us to do online content is to
実際、オンライン コンテンツを行う上で最も重要なことは、
to create or to find new pipelines
新しいパイプラインを作成または検索する
Bring the news that is originally in the country to the foreign country
もともと国内にあるニュースを外国に持っていく
ok help me next page
はい、次のページを手伝ってください
So what did the Taiwanese use the community to do?
では、台湾人はコミュニティを利用して何をしたのでしょうか？
The Taiwanese actually did quite a lot
台湾人は実に多くのことをした
Just last year, I actually did quite a lot of interesting things
ちょうど去年、私は実際にたくさんの興味深いことをしました
can help me next page
次のページを手伝ってください
Let's say we are the presidential palace
ここが大統領官邸だとしましょう
There is a Ukrainian blue flower
ウクライナの青い花があります
is to express a profound support for Ukraine
ウクライナへの深い支持を表明することです
then on the next page thanks
次のページではありがとう
Before our association made a picture called
私たちの協会が「」という写真を作る前に、
That is, Taiwan stands with Ukraine
つまり台湾はウクライナと肩を並べる
This is a picture of black bear and white he
これはツキノワグマとシロクマの写真です
Black bear represents Taiwan and Bai He represents Ukraine
ツキノワグマは台湾を代表し、白鶴はウクライナを代表します。
Then we call on netizens to post this picture on various
次に、この写真をさまざまなサイトに投稿するようネチズンに呼びかけます。
Posted under the tweets of various Ukrainian politicians
ウクライナのさまざまな政治家のツイートの下に投稿
Just leave a message to express an emotional support
精神的なサポートを表明するメッセージを残すだけです
Then this picture has more than 4,000 netizens who came to like it
そして、この写真には4,000人以上のネチズンがいいね！
is that we take a network action to express
それを表現するためにネットワークアクションを起こすということです
So Taiwan stands with Ukraine
だから台湾はウクライナと肩を並べる
can help me next page thanks
次のページを手伝ってください、ありがとう
Then we also observed that
それから私たちは次のことも観察しました
In fact, Taiwanese netizens are very concerned about Ukraine
実際、台湾のネットユーザーはウクライナについて非常に懸念している
Let's say in the first week of the war
戦争の最初の週に言ってみましょう
One of our Ukrainian friends sent us a photo
ウクライナ人の友人が写真を送ってくれました
He is a blogger who has been to Taiwan
彼は台湾に行ったことのあるブロガーです
He just likes it and says I'm still safe in Ukraine
彼はそれが気に入って、私はまだウクライナにいて安全だと言いました
At that time, there were probably more than a thousand Taiwanese netizens who liked it
当時、これを気に入った台湾のネットユーザーはおそらく千人以上いただろう
In fact, this network has
実際、このネットワークには、
The interesting thing is that even though you don't know him at all and you haven't met him
興味深いのは、たとえあなたが彼のことを全く知らず、会ったこともないにもかかわらず、
But because out of a humanitarian concern that everyone is human
しかし、人道的配慮から、誰もが人間であるため、
So you'll be safe as long as you see there are Ukrainians
だからウクライナ人がいる限りは安全だ
In fact, you will create a link with him through this posting net.
実はこの投稿ネットを通じて彼とリンクを張ることになります。
can help me next page
次のページを手伝ってください
That's right, we're actually helping too.
そうなんです、実は私たちもお手伝いさせていただいているんです。
Our association also often assists the Ukrainian community in Taiwan to forward some news
私たちの協会はまた、台湾のウクライナ人コミュニティがニュースを転送するのを支援することもよくあります。
Because they want to raise funds with the general public in Taiwan
台湾の一般の人たちと募金したいから
Or call on the people to take to the streets to support
あるいは街頭に出て支援するよう人々に呼びかける
To support Ukraine, this is our association to help forward a message
ウクライナを支援するために、これはメッセージの転送を支援する私たちの協会です
can help me next page
次のページを手伝ってください
Then in the NFT part, there are actually a lot of creative activities on the Internet
次に、NFTの部分では、実際にはインターネット上で多くの創造的な活動が行われています
It's a fundraiser for Ukraine.
ウクライナへの募金活動です。
Fundraising for Ukraine
ウクライナへの募金活動
Even though the amount last year was not very high
昨年の金額はそれほど高くなかったにもかかわらず、
But I think that is a new attempt by the Taiwanese community
でもこれは台湾人コミュニティの新しい試みだと思います
As far as NFT can be used for a charity-related fundraising operation
NFTが慈善活動に関連した募金活動に使用できる限り
there are many people
たくさんの人がいます
willing to participate
参加する意欲がある
ok help me next page
はい、次のページを手伝ってください
In these matters, Ukraine gave Taiwan
これらの問題で、ウクライナは台湾に譲歩した
what a revelation
なんという啓示だろうか
Revelation, in fact, we can see that
啓示では、実際、次のことがわかります。
Everyone in Ukraine
ウクライナの皆さん
The most important thing is to find a channel to spread the message
最も重要なことは、メッセージを広めるためのチャネルを見つけることです
Those things he he is not
彼は彼ではないそれらのもの
When something happens, you go find it
何かが起こったとき、あなたはそれを探しに行きます
It’s fine, he’s normal, so he needs to get ready slowly.
大丈夫、彼は正常だから、ゆっくり準備をする必要がある。
Or writing content or doing dissemination
コンテンツを書いたり、広めたりする
This kind of work also needs
このような作業も必要です
through daily practice
日々の練習を通して
And to think about these themes
そして、これらのテーマについて考えることは、
That needs to be prepared in advance.
それは事前に準備する必要があります。
So we talk about transition from peace to war
そこで私たちは平和から戦争への移行について話します
Normal and temporary conversion
通常および一時的な変換
ok help me next page
はい、次のページを手伝ってください
we are in this year
私たちは今年中にいます
Taiwan has done one
台湾は一つのことをやった
The group screen project of Taiwan Community Guardian
台湾コミュニティガーディアンのグループ上映プロジェクト
then we just want to say
それなら私たちはただ言いたいだけです
can come to upgrade
アップグレードに来ることができます
Taiwan's Cyber ​​Operations Propagation Capabilities
台湾のサイバー作戦伝播能力
then we are not fake news
それなら私たちはフェイクニュースではない
Because fake news is really a lot of people doing it
フェイクニュースは本当に多くの人がやっているから
in our opinion
我々の意見では
A small piece of Taiwan is what is needed
必要なのは台湾の小さなかけら
Let's discuss what we are going to do in this special war period
この特別な戦争期間に何をするかを話し合いましょう
Know how to do this kind of communication work
この種のコミュニケーション作業の方法を知っている
In this dissemination work, whether it is to make a report on domestic information
この普及活動では、国内の情報を報告するかどうか
Integrate, or in other words, foreign countries, is to make Taiwan's situation external
統合、つまり外国との統合とは、台湾の状況を外部化することである。
Communication maintains a degree of discussion throughout the international community
コミュニケーションにより、国際社会全体である程度の議論が維持される
These need to be cultivated slowly
これらはゆっくりと育てる必要があります
So we have a plan to launch a group screen this year
今年はグループ画面を立ち上げる予定です
can help me next page
次のページを手伝ってください
The group screen project is very grateful to more than 400 donors this year
今年はグループ上映プロジェクトに 400 名を超える寄付者が集まりました。
There is a plan to support this
これをサポートする計画があります
So we are doing a series of courses this year
そこで今年も一連の講座を開催します
can help me next page
次のページを手伝ってください
We have a series of courses this year
今年も様々な講座をご用意しております
That is for friends in different professional fields
それはさまざまな専門分野の友人のためのものです
So let's go and create communication courses that belong to different professional fields.
それでは、さまざまな専門分野に属するコミュニケーション コースを作成しましょう。
Then we are also developing a set of card games at the same time
それから、カードゲームのセットも同時に開発しています。
Well, this card game is actually for everyone to play different roles.
さて、このカードゲームは、実は全員がさまざまな役割を果たすためのものです。
Role
役割
like when a war breaks out
戦争が勃発したときのように
If you are usually a marketing communication person
普段マーケティングコミュニケーション担当者である場合
you are usually an engineer
あなたは普段エンジニアです
or you are usually a teacher
それともあなたは普段は教師ですか
you are in such a situation
あなたはそのような状況にいます
what can everyone do
みんなは何ができるの？
For example, if you are usually a teacher
たとえば、あなたが普段教師をしているとすると、
You may have to teach teachers in our courses
私たちのコースで教師に教えなければならない場合があります
In the final analysis, how to improve students
最終的には、生徒をどのように改善するかということです。
Ability to make media attempts or information interpretation
メディアの試みや情報の解釈を行う能力
There are actually different characters in this card game
このカードゲームには実際にはさまざまなキャラクターがいます
For example, there is another character called Overseas Taiwanese
たとえば、海外台湾人というキャラクターもいます。
The role of overseas Taiwanese
海外台湾人の役割
We will teach you in the course
講座内で教えていきます
Say if you are a study abroad student today
あなたが今日留学している学生だったら言ってみましょう
or Taiwanese working overseas
または海外で働く台湾人
How do you contact the local government media
地方自治体のメディアにどのように連絡しますか
Or to help with a translation job
または翻訳の仕事を手伝うため
So everyone can play in this card game
誰でもこのカードゲームで遊ぶことができます
or in our online courses
またはオンラインコースで
You can find different positions that may belong to you
あなたに当てはまるかもしれないさまざまなポジションを見つけることができます
or role
または役割
to do simulations to make predictions
予測を行うためにシミュレーションを行う
To rehearse the communication operations on the Internet in advance
インターネットでの通信操作を事前に予習するため
How to proceed like this
このように進める方法
OK, you can help me on the next page
OK、次のページで手伝ってください
that this is the last page
これが最後のページだということ
It's the conclusion, simply put
簡単に言えば結論です
Cognitive warfare is actually a
認知戦争というのは実は、
Topics that cannot be ignored in Taiwan
台湾で無視できない話題
It happens in our daily life
それは私たちの日常生活の中で起こります
Our daily life is
私たちの日常生活は、
need to identify information
情報を特定する必要がある
In addition to identifying information
情報を特定するだけでなく、
Become a Disseminator of Information
情報発信者になる
and being able to produce content from people
そして人々からコンテンツを生み出すことができる
This is one of the ways to raise the awareness of Taiwanese citizens
これは台湾国民の意識を高める方法の一つです
That's what I want to share with you the most today
それが今日私が皆さんに一番伝えたいことです
ok help me last page
OK、最後のページを手伝ってください
If you are online
オンラインの場合
If you are interested, you can go to our fan page
ご興味がございましたら、ファンページにアクセスしてください
You can go to our fan special
ファンスペシャルに行くことができます
is to refer to the digital diplomacy action plan
デジタル外交行動計画に言及すること
Then our IG and Twitter are both DG Diplo Lab
つまり、私たちのIGとTwitterは両方ともDG Diplo Labです
That or you have more questions
それか、もっと質問がありますか
or have something to discuss
または何か話し合うことがあります
You can remember our Email
私たちのメールを覚えておいてください
probably over here thanks
おそらくここにいるでしょう、ありがとう
Then we are very grateful to Chairman Guo for his sharing just now.
それでは、郭会長の今のお話に大変感謝いたします。
I think the game just now was just the board game
さっきのゲームはただのボードゲームだったと思う
I just remind you that there is a design
デザインがあることを思い出させてください
There seem to be many characters
登場人物もたくさんいるようです
That actually represents different people in our society.
それは実際、私たちの社会のさまざまな人々を表しています。
Then each of us might want to say
それから私たち一人一人が言いたいかもしれません
It seems that the war is far away from me
戦争は私から遠く離れたところにあるようです
or a real war
それとも本当の戦争か
I can't seem to do it when
できないようです
But I think this reminder just now is the discovery
でも今この思い出が発見だと思う
Not really
あまり
everyone at their job
みんな自分の仕事で
One of your usual professional abilities
あなたの通常の専門的能力の 1 つ
both may be available in time of war
戦争時にはどちらも利用できるかもしれない
let's play some roles
いくつかの役割を演じてみましょう
Let's be able to have some of this for the defense of Taiwan
台湾防衛のためにこれを少しでも手に入れましょう
helpful place
役に立つ場所
That just mentioned a lot of points
それは多くのポイントについて言及しただけです
Talking Screen Battle Transformation
トーキングスクリーンバトル変身
sometimes what is needed in wartime
戦時中に必要なこともある
It may be necessary to prepare in advance
事前に準備が必要な場合があります
Maybe it's not a wartime application
もしかしたら戦時中の申請ではないかもしれない
But you have to put this function first
ただし、この関数を最初に配置する必要があります
some infrastructure to design
設計するインフラストラクチャ
so i think next
だから次はこう思う
also the next speaker
次のスピーカーも
In fact, this is a very important reason
実はこれがとても重要な理由なのです
The previous Guo Dizhang mentioned
先ほど郭迪章が言及した
Ukraine seems to be making an App
ウクライナがアプリを作っているようだ
so that they can temporarily
一時的にできるように
Like can do something like identify the position of the enemy
敵の位置を特定するなどのことができる
Or let ordinary people know some situations
あるいは一般の人に状況を知らせる
You can use that App to repay
そのアプリを使って返済できます
As far as Taiwan is concerned, as far as we know
台湾に関して言えば、私たちが知っている限りでは、
Seems like the government doesn't have one like this
政府にはそのようなものはないようです
A digital tool that can be used by everyone
誰もが使えるデジタルツール
It doesn't matter if the government doesn't do it
政府がやらなくても問題ない
The great thing about Taiwan is that
台湾のすごいところは、
Our masters are among the people
私たちのマスターは人々の中にいます
Folks can do it
人々はそれを行うことができます
I think this is just wait a minute we're going to ask for this
これはちょっと待ってください、これからお願いすることになると思います
The place dad wants to share with us
お父さんが私たちと共有したい場所
What kind of way did he use to let us Taiwan
彼はどのような方法で私たちに台湾を許してくれたのでしょうか？
own folk have a tool
自国民は道具を持っている
can be a digital tool
デジタルツールになり得る
come and do a potential
来て潜在的なことをしてください
Maybe for now we can take one of the apps
おそらく今のところは、いずれかのアプリを使用できるでしょう
Effectively identify the enemy or this
敵を効果的に識別する
The method of group combat comes to us next please
次に集団戦闘の方法を説明します。
Thank you Dad
お父さんありがとう
so everyone can do
だから誰もができる
I will use my left palm
左手の手のひらを使います
try it first
まずは試してみる
wow, there's a nice screen on the front
うわー、前面に素晴らしいスクリーンがあります
Hello everyone, I am Abba
みなさんこんにちは、アバです
The front side, eh, the header video won’t come out
表側、えー、ヘッダー映像が出ないんです
That's okay, I'll just watch it
大丈夫、ただ見てあげるよ
what did you think
どう思いました
It doesn't matter
それは問題ではありません
oh yes
ああ、そうだね
eh yes
ええ、はい
good
良い
then i will start
それでは始めます
Hello everyone, I am Abba
みなさんこんにちは、アバです
Saints call me Abba
聖人たちは私をアバと呼んでいます
My real name is Xu Wulong
私の本名は徐武龍です
Then the first page of this head video
次に、このヘッダービデオの最初のページ
Its upper left corner is C700NAM
左上隅がC700NAMです
It means that this file is public
このファイルは公開されていることを意味します
so if given the chance
だから機会があれば
Then please host this header video
それでは、このヘッダービデオをホストしてください
can share with everyone
みんなと共有できる
The QR code in the lower right corner is
右下のQRコードは、
All relevant information scan this QR code
すべての関連情報はこの QR コードをスキャンしてください
Just put it in your mouth and there will be
口に入れるだけで、
ok then let's start
はい、それでは始めましょう
Okay, I'm going to start off by sharing a little bit
さて、少し共有することから始めましょう
some fumbling agendas of my own
私自身の手探りの計画
I think
私が思うに
From these years we know
過去数年間から私たちは知っています
Three needles have a chance
3本針にはチャンスがある
To be honest, I was very worried at first.
正直に言うと、最初はとても不安でした。
The more you worry the more you want to know
心配すればするほど知りたくなる
The more you understand, the more you worry
理解すればするほど不安になる
but you keep watching
でもあなたは見続けます
like my own case is
私自身の場合のように
you're worried you'll want to see what's going on
あなたは心配しています、何が起こっているのか見てみたいでしょう
What is the status of the input
入力状況はどうなっているのか
To put it simply, for example, should we flee or should we defend?
簡単に言うと、例えば逃げるべきか、守るべきか。
This is the basic question
これは基本的な質問です
I can't bear it, so I should run away, right?
耐えられないから逃げたほうがいいですよね？
But when you get to know more
でももっと詳しく知ると
Like I just said, I get to know more
先ほども言ったように、もっと知ることができます
In fact, besides worrying
実際、心配するだけでなく、
In fact, you will find that there is really very little you can do
実際、できることは本当にほとんどないことがわかるでしょう
Because each of these things seems to be a big thing
一つ一つが大きなことのように思えるから
It's like the president or something
社長か何かみたいだね
to be able to handle things that the government can handle
政府が対応できることは対応できる
what does that have to do with us
それは私たちと何の関係があるのですか
but you slowly find
でもあなたはゆっくりと見つけます
You will watch for a long time and you will find out that
ずっと見てると分かるよ
In fact, this can't work.
実際、これではうまくいきません。
what's the use of worrying
心配して何の役に立つの
most importantly
最も重要なこと
my idea is this
私のアイデアはこれです
don't worry if you want
ご希望であれば心配しないでください
So if you're worried then you have to do something
だから心配なら何かする必要がある
So I'm here to appeal to you by the way
それで、ところで私はあなたに訴えたいためにここにいます
the importance of action
行動の大切さ
must take action
行動を起こさなければならない
whatever you do whatever
何をしても何でも
you just start doing it
あなたはそれをやり始めるだけです
naturally less worry
自然と心配が減ります
That's what I think
それが私が思うことです
In the process of groping
手探りの過程で
first thing is this
まずはこれです
You have to find a way and take action
方法を見つけて行動を起こさなければなりません
But the first problem you will encounter is
しかし、最初に遭遇する問題は、
You really don't know what you can do
あなたは本当に自分に何ができるのか分かりません
You say like we engage in community
私たちがコミュニティに参加しているようにあなたは言います
You said I can for war something
あなたは戦争のために何かできると言いました
Yes, but the war is not here yet
はい、でも戦争はまだ始まっていません
What are you going for war for?
何のために戦争に行くのですか？
what do you want to notify
何を通知したいのですか
Then take a long time to learn
それから、学ぶのに長い時間がかかります
second thing i found
2番目に見つけたもの
In fact, you only need the second thing
実際に必要なのは 2 番目のことだけです
It's about finding a partner
それはパートナーを見つけることです
Intentional organization works well
意図的な組織化がうまく機能する
In fact, I have only entered this process.
実はこのプロセスに入っているのは私だけです
it's been a long time
おひさしぶりですね
That is to say, it took you a long time to find out
つまり、それを見つけるのに長い時間がかかったということです
In fact, the most important thing for you is
実際、あなたにとって最も重要なことは、
just to find those friends
その友達を見つけるためだけに
or someone with a heart
または心ある人
you will feel very strange
あなたはとても奇妙に感じるでしょう
There seems to be worried person
心配な人がいるようです
but you don't know who he is
でもあなたは彼が誰なのか知りません
Okay, so actually let's say later go to the black bear
さて、実際には後でツキノワグマに行くとしましょう
you will find
見つけるだろう
In fact, many caring people
実は思いやりのある人が多い
a lot of people with a lot of heart doing a lot of things
たくさんの心を持った人がたくさんのことをやっている
but you yourself behind the screen
でも、画面の向こうにいるのはあなた自身です
or how
あるいはどうやって
In fact, it is not easy for you to find out
実際のところ、それを知るのは簡単ではありません
but you just get out
でも出てくるしかない
went to an event or two
1つまたは2つのイベントに行きました
you will find
見つけるだろう
In fact, there are many people who are very close to you
実はあなたの近くにたくさんの人がいます
And everyone is doing a little bit of everything
そして誰もがあらゆることを少しずつやっています
and when you find out
そしてそれを知ったとき
when you start doing something
何かを始めるとき
your friends
あなたの友人
he will appear very strange
彼はとても奇妙に見えるだろう
like these today
今日はこんな感じで
many do not know
多くの人は知りません
Why have we been in touch before?
なぜ以前から連絡を取っていたのでしょうか？
that's it
それでおしまい
that he is not alone
彼は一人ではないということ
It's just that everyone compares
みんな比べてるだけだよ
That is, the Low profile is relatively indifferent
つまり、ロープロファイルは比較的無関心です
So the second thing is
2番目のことは
you like me my basic advice
あなたは私のことが好きです、私の基本的なアドバイス
is that you may say black bear
それはツキノワグマと言えるかもしれません
or other activities of private houses
または民家のその他の活動
you just try to participate
あなたはただ参加しようとしているだけです
you will find
見つけるだろう
this pipe will be fine
このパイプは大丈夫だろう
and most importantly
最も重要な
The most important thing is to say that we speak from a personal perspective
最も重要なことは、私たちが個人的な観点から話しているということです
when war really happens
戦争が本当に起こったとき
you really need friends
あなたには本当に友達が必要です
just need pipes
パイプだけが必要です
just need information
ただ情報が必要なだけ
just need these things
これらのものだけが必要です
But you usually know these people
しかし、あなたは通常、これらの人々を知っています
or have access to these organizations
またはこれらの組織にアクセスできる
What you get is the best and most first-hand information
得られるのは、最良かつ最も直接的な情報です
So this usually has to be cultivated
したがって、これは通常栽培する必要があります
Actually the last thing
実は最後に
It means you have to play your part
つまり、自分の役割を果たさなければならないということです
that is
あれは
20 million people, you have 20 million copies for 20 million people
2,000 万人なら、2,000 万人分の 2,000 万部のコピーがあります。
You don't have to think too much about what the government should do
政府が何をすべきかについてあまり考える必要はない
Actually, I think that thing is for me
実はそれが自分のためだと思う
Instead of telling people who to do
人々に何をすべきかを指示するのではなく
what should you do what organization do what government do
あなたは何をすべきか どの組織が何をすべきか 政府が何をすべきか
why don't you think about what you should do
何をすべきか考えてみませんか
You protect yourself, these are the most basic
自分の身は自分で守る、これが最も基本的なことです
So it's important that you do your part
だから、自分の役割を果たすことが重要です
what is that strength
その強さは何ですか
You have to define yourself to find
見つけるためには自分自身を定義する必要があります
like i say
私が言うように
Find the angle that suits you best
自分に最適な角度を見つけてください
Is my information strong?
私の情報は強力ですか？
Then of course I will start from the information
それからもちろん情報から始めます
you like me going to black bears
あなたは私がツキノワグマに行くのが好きですか
he has ambulance
彼は救急車を持っています
I'm not good at first aid, am I?
私は応急処置が苦手なんですよね？
You asked me to move people, I don’t want to move others, it’s fine
あなたは私に人を動かすように頼んだのですが、私は他の人を動かしたくありません、大丈夫です
Yes, that's why you will find it strange
そう、だから不思議に思うんだろうね
I have been engaged in information for so long, so of course it is not very good for me to come out and play a role like an information soldier
私はずっと情報に携わってきたので、表に出て情報戦士のような役割を演じるのはもちろん良くありません。
So the information warfare aspect is something I can ponder.
したがって、情報戦の側面については考えさせられます。
So my goal this year is to teach Black Bear all the information warfare courses.
したがって、私の今年の目標は、Black Bear に情報戦のコースをすべて教えることです。
Right, then there may be more professional scholars
そうですね、それならもっと専門的な学者がいるかもしれません
means find something you can do
できることを見つけるという意味です
I just want to let everyone know
ただみんなに知らせたいのです
In fact, the process should be very similar for everyone.
実際、このプロセスは誰にとっても非常に似ているはずです。
Then this is an introduction I gave you at the beginning, it is my own exploration experience
これは冒頭で紹介した、私自身の探検体験です
Alright, today's topic is some flexible use of Atec's digital willfulness
さて、今日のテーマはエイテックのデジタルの意志の柔軟な使い方です。
Well, first of all, let me tell you, please play the video for me, okay?
そうですね、まず最初に言っておきますが、ビデオを再生してください。
First let me show you what is called Atec
まず、Atec と呼ばれるものを紹介します。
Okay, this is a wait, it's an Atec one
さて、これは待ってください、これは Atec のものです
his demo video
彼のデモビデオ
he is an american
彼はアメリカ人です
A combat software used by American soldiers
アメリカ兵が使用する戦闘ソフトウェア
This is so clear
これはとても明らかです
You can see he's used by GIs
彼がGIに利用されているのがわかります
But actually we can also use
しかし、実際には次のこともできます。
Then he is very powerful
それから彼はとても強力です
Yes, he is already an actual combat base
はい、彼はすでに実戦基地です
You see he is battle proven
彼は戦いで証明されていることがわかります
That is to say, he is the actual combat base
つまり彼が実戦基地だ
he is available
彼は空いています
Not just toys or just games
おもちゃやゲームだけではありません
He's something that can really be used in battle
本当に戦闘で使える奴だ
Simply put, this is one of the American soldiers.
簡単に言えば、これはアメリカ兵の一人です。
combat software
戦闘ソフトウェア
You can see he has a base map
彼がベースマップを持っていることがわかります
You can switch between various basemaps
さまざまなベースマップを切り替えることができます
you can see he can know
あなたは彼が知っていることがわかります
This is 3D
これは 3D です
He can see 3D on his screen
彼は画面上で 3D を見ることができます
Each team can be seen on the map
各チームはマップ上で確認できます
Can measure distance
距離を測定できる
This is the position of each team
各チームの順位はこんな感じ
then this is the weather
それでは、これが天気です
he can
彼はできます
Incorporate current weather information
現在の気象情報を組み込む
then this is
それならこれは
this is
これは
Don't be like a camera or a drone's image
カメラやドローンの画像のようにならないでください
will directly see
直接見ます
So this is what it looks like when a lot of people are moving
たくさんの人が移動するとこんな感じになります
This is actually used in combat
これは実際に戦闘で使用されています
He has a lot of combinations
彼はたくさんの組み合わせを持っています
hardware
ハードウェア
You can see that there are a lot of icones here
ここにはたくさんのアイコンがあることがわかります
Then he is the standard interface of the US military
その後、彼は米軍の標準インターフェイスになります
so everyone you see
だから見てるみんな
will have the same meaning
同じ意味になります
Here is the comparison of all high-level
すべてのハイレベルの比較は次のとおりです
After you are blocked by three in a certain position
特定の位置で 3 人にブロックされた後
what else can you see
他に何が見えますか
Well, this is a bit like task assignment.
まあ、これはタスクの割り当てに似ています。
the location of everyone in
全員の位置
or the angle of a certain war zone
または特定の戦闘地域の角度
This is all the points, every running line, all the information on the line is available
これはすべてのポイント、すべての走行ライン、ライン上のすべての情報が利用可能です
Communication interface, he can communicate with other people at any time
通信インターフェース、いつでも他の人と通信できます
This is a drama, because he is a combat software, so you need to know where others are, where they are, and where they are defending
これはドラマです。彼は戦闘ソフトウェアなので、他の人がどこにいるのか、どこにいるのか、どこを守っているのかを知る必要があります。
This is from a drone, what the drone sees
これはドローンからのものです、ドローンが見ているもの
ok no more
はい、もうだめです
Okay, the software I just looked at
さて、先ほど見たソフトウェアです
Of course it's very cool, the video statement just now
もちろん、とてもクールです、今のビデオステートメント
Tell me this sounds like I developed it
これは私が開発したものだと言ってください
Don't get this wrong, it was developed by the US military
誤解しないでください、これは米軍が開発したものです
related to us
私たちに関係のある
Well, actually, I think we should talk about this
そうですね、実際にはこれについて話すべきだと思います
Its first thing is that just what does it matter to me
まず第一に、それは私にとって何が重要なのかということです
I can't use anything from the US military.
米軍のものは使えない。
Then what shall I say today?
では今日は何を話しましょうか？
What does digital humanity have to do with me?
デジタル ヒューマニティは私と何の関係があるのでしょうか?
Only when there is a relationship
ご縁がある場合のみ
ok this start
よし、これでスタート
What was that 3.6 Pro just now?
さっきの 3.6 Pro は何だったのでしょうか？
That's the video just now
それが今の動画です
Simply put it is
簡単に言えばそれは
GI Live Combat Software
GI ライブコンバット ソフトウェア
Stable and safe through the field test
フィールドテストによる安定性と安全性
Suitable for battle crystals
バトルクリスタルに最適
Everything about it is U.S. military standard
すべてが米軍規格です
ok what does that have to do with us
オーケー、それは私たちと何の関係があるの？
first thing
初めにすること
it is actually
それは実際にあります
like open source
オープンソースのような
If you have an Android phone, you can
Android スマートフォンをお持ちの場合は、
You can go directly to download and install
直接ダウンロードしてインストールできます
So you just wait and install it straight away
だから待ってすぐにインストールしてください
That
それか
That's because it's open source and free
それはオープンソースで無料だからです
So those things you just saw
それで、あなたが今見たもの
Actually eighty to ninety percent
実際には8割から9割
You're on your own Android phone and you're ready to go
自分の Android スマートフォンを使用しているので、準備は完了です。
so i'm not telling you a
だから私はあなたに言いません
an advanced thing far away no
遠く離れた先進的なもの
I'm talking to you about something you can use on your phone in ten minutes
携帯電話で 10 分で使えるものについて話しています
and it's free
そしてそれは無料です
ok what else does it have
はい、他に何がありますか
It has wind tag and itag so you iOS
Wind Tag と itag があるので、iOS
In fact, Windows can also be used, but it is not recommended
実はWindowsでも使用可能ですが、非推奨です
Basically you use the Android
基本的にはAndroidを使用します
good that
まあそれは
then you can imagine it that thing
そうすればそれを想像できます
if not in combat
戦闘中でない場合
What can it be used for? You can think about it
何に使えるか考えてみましょう
Things that can be used in battle are actually disaster prevention
実戦で使えるものは実は防災にもなる
Disaster relief, mountaineering, task force, stuff like that
災害救助、登山、対策本部、そのようなもの
In fact, they are very similar, the situation is very similar
実際、それらは非常に似ており、状況も非常に似ています
So actually you can use
したがって、実際に使用できます
then if we are really
もし私たちが本当にそうなら
When fighting happens, for example
例えば喧嘩が起きた時、
Here are a few examples. For example, you
以下にいくつかの例を示します。
well for example
まあたとえば
where is the supply where is the water
供給源はどこですか 水はどこですか
Well, for example, where is the well and where can I get it?
たとえば、井戸はどこにあり、どこで入手できますか?
get something then if you are
何かを手に入れてください。
If you walk outside, where is your partner?
外を歩いていると、パートナーはどこにいますか？
For example, suppose you have
たとえば、
there is that
それはあります
Air defense or something
防空か何か
For example, you are now in disaster
たとえば、あなたは今災害に遭っています。
Let's say you have a place where there's a bomb shelter
防空壕がある場所があるとします。
Or an evacuation facility, but that's not the point
あるいは避難施設だが、それは問題ではない
where is it the point is that it's inside now
それはどこですか、要は今それが中にあるということです
Is there anything else?
他に何かありますか？
Is there still room, is there enough water in it?
まだスペースはありますか、水は十分ですか？
Is there something so your information
何かあなたの情報はありますか
needs to be updated, then we are
更新する必要がある場合は、
These things in our current system are very weak
私たちの現在のシステムのこれらのものは非常に弱いです
But it is very easy for you to use this software
しかし、このソフトウェアを使用するのは非常に簡単です
That's where this software comes in handy
そこでこのソフトウェアが役に立ちます
Then it's written here, since it's combat software
それなら戦闘ソフトだからここに書いてあるよ
So of course it can happen during combat
もちろん戦闘中に起こる可能性もあります
great use
素晴らしい使い方
For example, it is more useful for our folks to use it.
たとえば、私たちにとっては、それを使用する方が便利です。
For example, we just said that the communication software is broken
たとえば、先ほど通信ソフトウェアが壊れたと言いました。
What to do if LINE is broken
LINEが切れた場合の対処法
LINE down doesn’t mean your internet is down
LINEがダウンしてもインターネットがダウンするわけではありません
Maybe it's just that his server is down
もしかしたらサーバーがダウンしているだけかもしれません
Maybe it's just that LINE was killed
LINEが潰れただけかもしれない
or how
あるいはどうやって
Well, it's software like this
とまあ、こんなソフトです
It doesn't matter you just need to connect to the Internet
インターネットに接続するだけで問題ありません
Even if your network is not connected, it can pass through
ネットワークが接続されていない場合でも通過できます
Well, you, so if you're in mission command
そうですね、あなたがミッションコマンドにいるなら
It's actually very useful
実はとても便利なんです
Well, what this page actually tells you is
さて、このページが実際に伝えていることは、
it has many uses
多くの用途があります
And now you can start using
そして今すぐ使い始めることができます
The point is how much you you master it
どれだけ使いこなせるかがポイント
Well, I just watched his video
さて、ちょうど彼のビデオを見ました
Is there an official video of him
彼の公式ビデオはありますか
Can you tell me that that can really work?
それが本当に効果があると言えますか？
It's just that he's because sometimes the film shows well
それはただ、時々映画がよく見えるからです
In fact, it can't be used
実際には使えない
So the first thing we do is we go and try
だから私たちが最初にやることは、行って試してみることです
We actually installed 40 basemaps
実際に 40 のベースマップをインストールしました
Make sure its basemap is available
ベースマップが利用可能であることを確認してください
We really did these synergies
私たちは本当にこれらの相乗効果を実現しました
know each
それぞれを知っています
Let's say this example
この例で言ってみましょう
I was in Operation Blue Tit at Black Bear Academy
私はブラック・ベア・アカデミーで青シジュウカラ作戦に参加していました
ok then what
わかりました、それではどうしますか
I'll just take two of us
二人だけ連れて行きます
Then one of the things that was played in the blue bird operation
それから青い鳥作戦で行われたものの一つ
just anyway
とにかく
The People's Liberation Army is arresting people
人民解放軍が人々を逮捕している
we just hide there
私たちはそこに隠れるだけです
I got caught
捕まってしまいました
after catch
キャッチ後
I just look at the software
ソフトウェアを見るだけです
so i can know where my friends are
そうすれば友達がどこにいるかを知ることができます
so you know instantly where the other is
だから相手がどこにいるのかすぐに分かります
It actually matters when something actually happens
実際に何かが起こったときが重要です
those streams
それらの流れ
Indeed, this thing can also move
なるほど、これも動くんですね
Hardware and software integration
ハードウェアとソフトウェアの統合
After we get acquainted with this
これを知ってから
I know how to integrate
統合する方法を知っています
This page is actually very important
このページは実はとても重要です
that's it
それでおしまい
it actually
それは実際に
For example, you have a software like this
たとえば、次のようなソフトウェアがあります
It says this is a tank
これは戦車だそうです
Then it says red is the enemy
すると赤が敵だという。
green may be allies
緑は味方かもしれない
then this tank
それからこのタンク
But the problem is you only look at tanks
しかし問題は、あなたが戦車しか見ていないことです
It this for example this tank is
たとえばこのタンクはこれです
which type
どのタイプ
that is
あれは
It means that the icon you think is the same as the icon that others think
それはあなたが考えるアイコンと他の人が考えるアイコンが同じであることを意味します
See you both have to recognize the same thing
ほら、両方とも同じことを認識する必要があります
No, he thinks the green is the friendly army, you think the green is the enemy, so what to do?
いいえ、彼は緑が味方の軍隊だと考えていますが、あなたは緑が敵だと考えています。それではどうすればよいでしょうか?
So the standard for the entire interface the standard for the entire format
したがって、インターフェイス全体の標準はフォーマット全体の標準になります
It's actually a very important thing
実はとても大切なことなんです
That's why it's important that he meets U.S. military standards
だからこそ、彼が米軍の基準を満たすことが重要である
I mean, any of you so-called, let's say, military-like people
つまり、いわゆる軍人風の人々のいずれかです。
He sees this interface, he understands it at a glance
彼はこのインターフェースを見て、一目で理解しました
He won't need retraining and it's all the same
彼には再トレーニングの必要はないし、すべて同じだ
Have relevant training
関連するトレーニングを受ける
This is just watched
これはただ見ているだけです
This is something really cool that we will find if we do GIS
これは本当に素晴らしいことです。GIS をやれば見つかるでしょう。
That is, since he can be here, like saying you are in the mountains
それは、彼がここにいることができるから、あなたが山にいると言っているようなものです
You can know that we are in the mountains, you can't see behind the mountains
私たちが山の中にいることはわかりますが、山の後ろは見えません
But how do you know that place you can see it or not
でも、その場所が見えるか見えないかをどうやって知るのですか？
He's here, this place, where he stands in the middle
彼はここ、この場所、真ん中に立っている
Green is what he can see, red is what he can't see
緑は見えるもの、赤は見えないもの
may be blocked by mountains
山に遮られるかもしれない
This is very useful when you are fighting, right?
これは戦闘するときにとても便利ですよね？
You can hit you, you can't hit you
あなたはあなたを殴ることができます、あなたはあなたを殴ることはできません
You have to see if you can hit or not
ヒットできるかどうかを確認する必要があります
these are useful
これらは便利です
Then this is task cutting
それではタスクカットです
I just saw this on video
さっきビデオで見たんだけど
I'm just going to say a little more here
ここでもう少しだけ言っておきます
For example, this one on the right
たとえば、これは右側です
The one on the right is actually what it can be
右側のものは実際にそれができるものです
It means that you only need to connect in
つまり、接続するだけで済みます
you can message someone
誰かにメッセージを送ることができます
So a group of people can communicate with each other
人々のグループが互いにコミュニケーションできるようにするため、
It actually doesn't need a line or anything
実際には線も何も必要ありません
You just add it and you can basically do a group chat
追加するだけで基本的にグループチャットができます
What I saw just now were all other people's videos
今見たのは全部他人の動画だった
cutout of
の切り抜き
Now let's show you an example of our own use
それでは、私たち自身の使用例を紹介しましょう
what is this example
この例は何ですか
This example is that I took it and I went to Hualien to play
この例は私がそれを持って花蓮に遊びに行ったものです
It's not playing anymore
もう再生されていません
just go to a meeting
ただ会議に行くだけ
When I go to a meeting, I will
会議に行くときは、
Let's have a meeting. It's always delicious food in Hualien.
打ち合わせをしましょう。花蓮はいつも美味しい食べ物です。
I'll just go eat and take a picture of it
食べて写真撮るだけだよ
What you can see is here
見えるものはここにあります
Never mind
どうでも
You can see there is a ghost machine here, there are a lot of pictures
ここにゴーストマシンがあるのがわかります。写真がたくさんあります
Then the photos will be on the table
それから写真はテーブルの上に置かれます
will show up showing it's a photo
写真であることを示して表示されます
show its name
その名前を表示します
And more importantly, and you see this
そしてもっと重要なことは、これを見ればわかります
This so-called trajectory can be replayed
このいわゆる軌跡は再現可能です
means you can
できるという意味です
you can
あなたはできる
Afterwards, you can know where you are at what time
その後、自分が何時にどこにいるのかを知ることができます
Where was the upper echelon at that time
当時の上層部はどこにあったのか
all this is known
これはすべて知られています
More importantly, these whole packages
さらに重要なのは、これらのパッケージ全体
it can be copied
コピーできます
I'll go to Hualien Wan to record this
これを録音するために花蓮湾に行きます
Then what
じゃあ何
when it's over i just push a button
それが終わったらボタンを押すだけです
Pack
パック
I'm just a bag
私はただのバッグです
Then I can pass this packet on to others
そうすれば、このパケットを他の人に渡すことができます
so think about it
だからそれについて考えてください
Let's say we go do some scouting
偵察に行くとしましょう
or do something
または何かをする
what you've done
あなたがしたこと
how do you give the information to others
他の人にどのように情報を提供しますか
No, or a group of people working together
いいえ、または一緒に働く人々のグループ
Suppose you collaborate to explore a thing
協力して何かを探索するとします
Or let's say you cooperate to do an inventory
あるいは、棚卸しに協力するとします。
where is it near here
この近くのどこにありますか
So your mask map is ready
これでマスクマップの準備が完了しました
Of course the masks were made very well.
もちろんマスクもとても丁寧に作られていました。
But the problem is when you don't have a mask system
しかし、問題はマスクシステムがない場合です
what are you going to do
何をする？
It's very simple to use this thing
これの使い方はとても簡単です
You just
あなたはただ
Everyone has a machine like this
みんなこんな機械持ってるよ
Then everyone's eyes should feel
そうすれば皆の目はこう感じるはずだ
Let's say I'm in charge of taking inventory of this area.
私がこの分野の棚卸しを担当しているとします。
You are in charge of taking stock of that area
あなたはその領域の状況を把握する責任があります
Hit everyone when they go
そして、彼らが去ったときに全員を殴ります
After I clicked, I took stock of the information
クリックした後、情報を確認しました
I will pass it on to you
あなたにお渡しします
and then both to the same person
そして両方とも同じ人に
The same person has the right to merge the version
同じ人がバージョンをマージする権利を持っています
So that's where he's pretty good
そこが彼がかなり優れているところだ
There is a picture in the middle
真ん中に写真があります
Then this is like this picture
そうすると、この写真のようになります
he has many maps
彼はたくさんの地図を持っています
For example, when climbing mountains, I like to use Lu map.
たとえば、山に登るときは Lu マップを使用するのが好きです。
Then, for example, some folks are
それから、例えば、何人かの人々は、
For example, if you want to see the river, you have to look at the government
たとえば、川を見たいなら政府を見なければなりません
this kind of map
このような地図
Then Google is everyone's favorite
Google はみんなのお気に入りです
Sometimes you want to watch satellites
衛星放送を見たいときもある
Sometimes you want to look at drawings
たまには図面も見たくなるよね
so many maps
とてもたくさんの地図
He actually needs to be easily switched
彼は実際には簡単に切り替える必要がある
Then he can switch this thing at any time.
そうすれば、いつでもこれを切り替えることができます。
import at any time
いつでもインポート
the one on the upper right
右上のもの
This one in the upper right corner actually says
右上隅にあるこれは実際にこう言っています
He is the so-called packing
彼はいわゆるパッキンです
That is, you can combine a lot of information into one package
つまり、多くの情報を 1 つのパッケージにまとめることができます
Just connect and download, after downloading, you will have all the information
接続してダウンロードするだけで、ダウンロード後にすべての情報が得られます
What's in this bag depends on what you packed in the first place.
このバッグの中に何が入っているかは、最初に何を詰めたかによって決まります。
For example, you can let me give an example
たとえば、例を挙げてみましょう
Okay, here it is, right down the middle, it's the Water Resources Department.
はい、こちら、真ん中あたり、水資源局です。
This is, for example, the data of the guards.
これは、たとえば警備員のデータです。
This is open data, so we import the open data directly.
これはオープンデータなので、オープンデータを直接インポートします。
Others don’t have to do anything to get open information and get things
他の人はオープンな情報を入手したり、物事を入手したりするために何もする必要がありません
No, he just keeps coming in and opening it
いいえ、彼はただ入ってきて開け続けているだけです
There are guards all over his map
彼のマップのいたるところに警備員がいます
Let's say you think of it as, suppose you're all right now
あなたは次のように考えたとします。今は大丈夫だとします
You have a supply point, all kinds of supply points
供給ポイントがあります、あらゆる種類の供給ポイントがあります
Now you probably have any supplies in there, you make it into a bag
おそらくそこに必需品が入っているので、それをバッグに入れます
As soon as the person enters the house, as soon as he opens it, there will be
人が家に入るとすぐに、家を開けるとすぐに、
Where is he nearby? He is clear.
彼は近くにどこにいますか? 彼ははっきりしています。
that's where oral
そこが口頭です
OK, let me tell you what we can do.
OK、私たちに何ができるかを教えましょう。
First let me tell you who we are
まず私たちが何者であるかをお話しさせてください
Actually we are just us we play these things
実際、私たちはただ私たちであり、これらのことをプレイしています
Basically just a few people, a few engineers
基本的には数人、数人のエンジニア
Some do system management, some do software development, some do hardware design
システム管理を行う人、ソフトウェア開発を行う人、ハードウェア設計を行う人もいます
Experts with drones
ドローンの専門家
Then our spirit is open source
そうすれば、私たちの精神はオープンソースになります
So you can see that the slideshow just now is open
先ほどのスライドショーが開いていることがわかります
The links that you click on in the slideshow, everything is open.
スライドショー内でクリックしたリンクはすべて開いています。
All that we learn is open
私たちが学ぶことはすべてオープンです
what were we doing a while ago
私たちは少し前に何をしていましたか
We call it free health account stacking
私たちはそれを無料の健康アカウントスタッキングと呼んでいます
For example, you are now listening to my talk about playing this thing
たとえば、あなたは今、これを演奏することについての私の話を聞いています。
It feels good
いい感じです
Is it easy to use?
使いやすいですか？
Although it is enough to install it, will you use it after installing it?
インストールするだけでは十分ですが、インストールした後、使用しますか？
In fact, when we played with this thing at the beginning, I found that
実際、最初にこれを使って遊んだとき、次のことがわかりました。
Actually it's not that easy
実際にはそれほど簡単ではありません
it's a bit of a barrier to entry
それは少し参入障壁です
Mainly because I don't know why
主に理由がわからないからです
It's military software after all it's not enough
やっぱり軍用ソフトじゃ物足りない
It's well designed, but it's not clear enough
うまく設計されていますが、十分に明確ではありません
it won't shoot you a youtube video saying
YouTube ビデオを撮影することはできません。
you just play like this
あなたはただこのように遊ぶだけです
Or you are hard to help with the manual
または、マニュアルを手伝うのが難しい場合
dozens of pages like this
このようなページが数十ページあります
you just think it's
あなたはただそう思っているだけです
why 20 minutes
なぜ20分なのか
how to get it fast
早く手に入れる方法
Well, to put it simply
まあ、簡単に言うと
Wired sparring We probably each
有線スパーリング 私たちはおそらくそれぞれ
every two to three weeks or a month
2～3週間または1か月ごと
There's going to be an online duel so you can connect.
オンラインデュエルがあるので接続できます。
Then you don't need to know anything, just take your
何も知る必要はありません。
Enjoy the mobile phone to come in and it will be two hours
携帯電話を楽しんで来てください、それは2時間になります
online you are in your own home within two hours
オンラインなら2時間以内に自宅に戻れます
You promise to use it, that is, you will use the important things
使うと約束する、つまり大切なものは使うということ
We have such online sparring, I won’t talk about the others
オンラインスパーリングはたくさんあるので、他のことについては話しません
These are things that we've already done
これらは私たちがすでに行ったことです
We do this online sparring, and it's very touching to say that
私たちはオンラインでスパーリングを行っていますが、こう言えるのはとても感動的です
We later had feedback that some police
その後、一部の警察からのフィードバックがありました。
some policemen in their own
一部の警察官は自分自身で
I started using something like this in my work
仕事でこのようなものを使い始めました
I said, how do you know this place? He said that it was you who held the online sparring.
「どうしてここを知っているのですか？」と言うと、オンラインスパーリングを開催したのはあなただと言いました。
After they come in, they find it useful after they're done.
入社してから、終わった後も役に立つことがわかります。
I'll do it myself later, and then I'll do it
後は自分でやってみます。
So it's actually doable, it's proven to be doable
つまり、それは実際に実行可能であり、実行可能であることが証明されています
What does this have to do with digital willfulness? Today is not about digital willfulness.
これはデジタルの故意とどのような関係があるのでしょうか? 今日の話題はデジタルの故意に関するものではありません。
In fact, it should be said that the community is very flexible.
実際、コミュニティは非常に柔軟であると言うべきです。
But the community is actually very unstructured.
しかし、コミュニティは実際には非常に構造化されていません。
And the most important thing is the structure
そして最も重要なのは構造です
Difficult to compose in times of war
戦時中は作曲が難しい
Architectural things take a lot of time to plan
建築物は計画に時間がかかる
what to build
何を構築するか
Like the Su Hui diplomacy just now
さっきの蘇恵外交みたいに
what they are doing
彼らは何をやってるの
That's the architectural thing
それが建築的なものです
your structural stuff
あなたの構造的なもの
when you established very early
非常に早い段階で確立したとき
When something happens, everyone will come
何かあったらみんな来るよ
That's if you don't have this structure
この構造が無い場合は
you panic when it happens
それが起こるとパニックになります
It's the same with this kind of software
この種のソフトも同様です
You usually play and practice
普段は遊んだり練習したりするのですが、
well that might be used for paintball
まあ、それはペイントボールに使えるかもしれない
What are you climbing again?
また何を登るのですか？
you preschool entertainment
あなたは就学前のエンターテイメントです
but when it actually happens
しかしそれが実際に起こると
This time things are very useful
今回もとても便利な物ばかりです
let me tell you
言っておくけど
Let's not talk about this on the spot
その場ではこの話はやめましょう
because there is no time
時間がないので
I'll just talk about Uber
ウーバーについてだけ話します
while in ukraine
ウクライナにいる間
that time they had a battle
その時彼らは戦いをした
Just what, what, shield, Nez, what battle
いったい何、何、盾、ネズ、何の戦い
Then the black army is very strange
それから黒軍は非常に奇妙です
He suddenly one night at the same time
彼はある晩、同じ時間に突然
Didn't he say that all the tanks were blown up by him?
彼はすべての戦車が彼によって爆破されたと言いませんでしたか？
I saw it then
その時見たよ
just a headache
ただの頭痛
Because we do information systems
情報システムをやっているので
we know very well
私たちはよく知っています
it's very difficult
とても難しい
How do you coordinate so much information
大量の情報をどうやって調整するのですか
then let all the missiles
それからすべてのミサイルを発射しましょう
at the same gun at the same time
同じ銃で同時に
hit different tanks
さまざまな戦車を攻撃する
then they say
それから彼らは言います
They're called the Uber system
それらはUberシステムと呼ばれています
at that time we
その時私たちは
we thought wow
私たちはすごいと思いました
it's amazing
すごい
how the hell is this done
いったいどうやってこれが行われるのか
found out later
後でわかった
After I started to know this software
このソフトを知り始めてから
Is this piece of cake good?
このケーキは美味しいですか？
use this thing
これを使ってください
no development at all
全く発展が無い
Here's how to do it
やり方はこうです
Just say yes, everyone has
はい、と言ってください、誰もが持っています
let's say
まあ言ってみれば
we say in the message
私たちはメッセージで言います
we are at 4 a.m.
私たちは午前4時です
we are going to shoot
私たちは撃ちます
For example, this battlegroup
たとえば、この戦闘グループ
4:00 a.m. I'm going to fire
午前4時、発砲するよ
it's 12 o'clock
12時です
Commanders please yourself
指揮官たち、どうぞご自由に
Choose which tank you want to fight
戦いたい戦車を選択してください
That drone flew over
あのドローンが飛んできた
he will find
彼は見つけます
he will soar
彼は舞い上がるだろう
Bahia are these tanks here
バイーアはここにある戦車です
Then the commander would say, for example
すると指揮官は、例えばこう言います。
everyone chooses
みんなが選ぶ
After the election, someone must reveal it, right?
選挙が終わったら、誰かがそれを明らかにしなければなりませんよね？
So he communicated in the group and said
そこで彼はグループ内でコミュニケーションをとり、こう言いました。
so you hit him
それであなたは彼を殴りました
he hit him
他打他
Okay, let's talk at 3:00
はい、3時に話しましょう
Don't move, everyone, start moving at 4 o'clock
みんな動かないで4時から動き始めてね
4 o'clock, one hit is not all dead
4:00キル
It's that simple
それはとても簡単です
no customization, no need for anything
カスタマイズの必要はありません、何もありません
The things just mentioned are all built-in in the AT software.
今述べたものはすべて AT ソフトウェアに組み込まれています。
All do not need F, this is strong software and weak software
全てにFは必要ありません、これは強いソフトウェアと弱いソフトウェアです
You just saw this and you knew it
これを見ただけでわかったでしょう
If you are fighting, you are
戦っているなら、あなたはそうだ
On the other side of Russia, you are
ロシアの反対側にはあなたがいます
You are on the Russian side, you don't have this thing
あなたはロシア側にいます、あなたはこれを持っていません
Or do you wish you were Ukraine with this thing
それとも、ウクライナ人だったらよかったと思いますか？
I don't want to be the one I don't have, I feel beaten to death
私は自分にないものにはなりたくない、死ぬほど殴られたと感じる
This is, and most importantly, this is open
これは、そして最も重要なことですが、これはオープンです
That
それか
This is the basic reference
これが基本的なリファレンスです
Anyway, this is pretty useful, but
とにかく、これはかなり便利ですが、
I've always found it weird to promote this thing
これを宣伝するのはいつも奇妙だと思っていた
he is open
彼はオープンです
no money
お金がない
Then I don't know why everyone doesn't know
じゃあなんでみんな知らないのか分からない
Then when I started learning this, I wanted to say I don't know
それから私はこれを学び始めました、私は知りませんと言いたいです
It is because this one is very new, too new, so people don't know
これはとても新しい、新しすぎるので人々が知らないからです
no i touched his
いいえ、私は彼に触れました
He has been out for two or three years
彼は2、3年離れていた
And what's more, I have been promoting him for more than half a year
しかも、私は半年以上彼を宣伝し続けています
In fact, I guess almost no one knows now.
実際、今ではほとんど誰も知らないと思います。
i feel weird
変な気がする
Anyway, the most important thing is
とにかく、一番大切なのは、
The application promotion at the top is the first link at the beginning
上部のアプリケーションのプロモーションは最初の最初のリンクです
And the last practice guide is basically
そして最後の練習ガイドは基本的には
when we practiced online
オンラインで練習したとき
Record
記録
Then if you say I can't wait for your online sparring
じゃあオンラインスパーリングが待ちきれないって言うなら
You click on the link below
下のリンクをクリックすると、
In fact, if you follow that, you can already do it.
実際、それに従えば、すでにそれを行うことができます。
Actually, you don't even need to come in to practice.
実際には、練習に来る必要さえありません。
that's it
それでおしまい
ok 20 minutes yes yes yes
オーケー、20分、はい、はい
thanks to his dad for sharing i think this
これを共有してくれた彼のお父さんに感謝します
I just had this and secretly pressed download
これを持っていてこっそりダウンロードを押しました
Sure enough, as you said, someone needs to be brought in the door
確かに、あなたが言ったように、誰かをドアに連れてくる必要があります
Anyway, wait a minute after our event
とにかく、イベントが終わったらちょっと待ってください
maybe a few minutes for us to be there
おそらく到着までに数分かかるでしょう
This more people know this software
このソフトウェアをより多くの人が知ることができます
But I think this thing is
しかし、私はこのことはそうだと思う
Although we don't want
私たちは望んでいませんが
we actually use it in wartime
実際に戦時中に使用しています
because we don't want war
私たちは戦争を望んでいないからです
But actually the other way around
しかし実際はその逆です
Maybe the more people we had before the war even happened
もしかしたら戦前にもっと人がいたかもしれない
get ready for war
戦争の準備をする
War is less likely
戦争の可能性は低い
why? because you raised the enemy
なぜ? あなたが敵を育てたからです
to attack your cost
コストを攻撃するために
when he finds out
彼がそれを知ったとき
Whoever I'm going to attack is ready
私が攻撃する相手は誰でも準備はできています
When my chances of success are low
成功の可能性が低いとき
Otherwise, there will be no war
そうでなければ戦争は起こらない
So I think it's a
だから私はそれはだと思います
why are we here now
なぜ私たちは今ここにいるのか
Another reason
もう一つの理由
Then I think the one just before
それから、直前のものだと思います
whether habba
ハバかどうか
Or we've had the holidays above and it's all good
あるいは、上記の休暇を過ごしたので大丈夫です
peacetime conversion
平時からの転換
In fact, many things we usually
実際、私たちが普段行っている多くのことは、
We may all use things on a daily basis
私たちは皆、日常的に物を使っているかもしれません
Maybe we didn't necessarily think to say
たぶん、私たちは必ずしもこう言うつもりはなかったのでしょう
It turns out that this thing was during the war
これは戦時中のものだったことが判明
or in possibly gray
あるいは灰色の場合もあります
When faced with the gray dangerous hybrid battle
灰色の危険なハイブリッドの戦いに直面したとき
can come in handy
役に立つかもしれない
So I think this is what we are looking forward to today
これが今日私たちが楽しみにしていることだと思います
Share with you the next details
次の詳細をお知らせします
Because like Qsearch
Qsearchのように
Meaning we are now very much
つまり、私たちは今とても
The industry is
業界は
A community monitoring that will be used
使用されるコミュニティモニタリング
Or a tool to understand the voice of the community
またはコミュニティの声を理解するためのツール
Then if there is a war
それで戦争が起きたら
A monitoring tool for a community like this
このようなコミュニティのための監視ツール
what kind of role can we play
私たちはどんな役割を果たせるか
I think this is worth listening to
これは聞く価値があると思います
Then let's welcome Director Cai first, thank you
それでは、まず蔡監督をお迎えしましょう、ありがとうございます
will there be a picture here
ここに写真はありますか
good
良い
Hello everyone
こんにちは、みんな
Hello friends online
オンラインの友達、こんにちは
yes it is
はい、そうです。
Like this one just lying on the tide
たった今潮に横たわっている人のように
In fact, we are the Cunzuo introduced by the chief operating officer Hong.
実は私達はレッド作戦部長から紹介されたクンズオです。
Monitoring of online information
オンライン情報の監視
That is of course based on public information.
もちろん公開情報に基づいたものです。
Either that or I can already
それか、もうできるよ
Intrude into the conversation group that may be LINE
LINEと思われる会話グループに乱入
Actually, I'm still in the commercial field
実は私はまだ商業分野にいます
There will be some customers who have this kind of demand
このようなご要望をお持ちのお客様もいらっしゃるでしょう
then i will call
それでは電話します
just tell them
ただ彼らに伝えてください
Maybe join the official organization on the other side
向こうの正式な組織に入るかもしれない
You will have this opportunity to enjoy this right like this
この機会にぜひお楽しみください
Yes, but we still don't have this thing in Taiwan
はい、でも台湾にはまだこれがありません
So we're collecting a lot of publicly available information
そこで私たちは公開されている情報をたくさん集めています
That's actually because now
それは実際に今だからです
I believe everyone feels the information explosion
誰もが情報の爆発を感じていると思います
Especially in recent times, there are too many
特に最近は多すぎる
Various information about a series of societies
一連の学会に関する各種情報
it just keeps happening
それはただ起こり続けます
And so actually some people
そして実際に何人かの人々は
That's when the information can be too explosive
そういうときは情報が爆発的すぎる可能性があります
he is easily distracted or frustrated
彼はすぐに気が散ったりイライラしたりする
Or it's just that he can't absorb it like this
それとも、彼がこのようにそれを吸収できないだけですか
That's too far
それは遠すぎる
Let's go back to today's topic
今日の話題に戻りましょう
Then introduce our company first
それではまず当社の紹介をさせていただきます
That is to say, when it comes to cognitive operations,
つまり、認知操作に関して言えば、
In fact, the election campaign is also a cognitive war
実は選挙戦は認知戦争でもある
Then we are indeed the space-time background of software development
そうすれば、私たちはまさにソフトウェア開発の時空の背景です
It happened to be 2014
たまたま2014年のことでした
that year
その年
It's the mayoral race
市長選挙だよ
That's a motley crew
多彩な乗組員ですね
A motley crew with a consensus
コンセンサスを持った雑多な乗組員
That's against another candidate Lian Shengwen like this
別の候補者リアン・シェンウェンとの対戦はこんな感じ
In that year, I thought I should remind everyone of the background of time and space.
この年、私は皆さんに時間と空間の背景を思い出してもらいたいと考えました。
In fact, Facebook did not have a large number of commercial advertisements in that year.
実際、この年、Facebook は多くの商業広告を掲載していませんでした。
Even many brands have not yet established a fan industry
多くのブランドでもまだファン産業が確立されていない
what is the reason
理由は何ですか
They were still stealing vegetables back then.
彼らは当時もまだ野菜を盗んでいました。
or the end of the restaurant
またはレストランの終わり
Everyone is still playing online games
誰もがまだオンラインゲームをプレイしています
yes but it is
はい、でもそうです
just because you know
あなたが知っているという理由だけで
Candidate Ke Wenzhe did not have so many resources at that time
当時、柯文哲候補にはそれほど多くのリソースがなかった
He may have political ideas or something
彼は政治的思想か何かを持っているのかもしれない
Then he will call a group of people
それから彼は人々のグループに電話します
Then these people started using the Internet
その後、これらの人々はインターネットを使い始めました
Platforms like this are starting to advocate
このようなプラットフォームが提唱し始めています
then go tell everyone
それからみんなに言いに行って
then this is one such candidate
それならこれもその候補の一つです
what is the ideal of this candidate
この候補者の理想は何ですか
So what are his expectations for the municipality?
それでは、彼は自治体に対して何を期待しているのでしょうか？
or what will he do in the future
あるいは彼は将来何をするつもりですか
Then you see he is doing cognitive warfare
そうすれば、彼は認知戦争を行っていることがわかります
He's just telling everyone
彼はただみんなに言ってるだけだよ
then why do you support me
ではなぜ私をサポートするのですか
So in fact, the market share of the campaign brand
実際、キャンペーンブランドの市場シェアは
He is cognitive warfare
彼は認知戦争です
Of course there are some confrontations between countries
もちろん国家間の対立もある
He is also a cognitive operator
彼は認知オペレーターでもあります
It just means that we usually compare
それは単に私たちが通常比較していることを意味します
I think this distance is far
この距離は遠いと思う
Or rather don't know how to deal with
というか対処法がわからない
so maybe on this
だから多分これについて
I think the better way
より良い方法だと思います
It's our open discussion
それは私たちのオープンディスカッションです
Then see how
それでは、その方法を見てみましょう
Can go for drills and upgrades
練習してレベルアップできる
optimize your awareness
意識を最適化する
ok that pair
わかりました、そのペア
just to introduce
紹介するだけ
We started in 2014
2014年にスタートしました
collect this information
この情報を収集する
There was Facebook in the beginning
もともとフェイスブックはあった
That's quite a lot now
今ではかなり多いですね
Actually we're not just political type clients
実際のところ、私たちは単なる政治的な顧客ではありません
Mainly commercial customers
主に法人顧客
the needs of commercial customers
商業顧客のニーズ
Still contains quite a lot of other media
まだかなり多くの他のメディアが含まれています
For example, in recent years, IG YouTube
たとえば、近年では、IG YouTube
In fact, more and more users like this
実際、このようなユーザーが増えています
that or
それか
online forums
オンラインフォーラム
Things like PTD cards
PTDカードのようなもの
There is still a need for business intelligence gathering
ビジネスインテリジェンス収集の必要性は依然としてある
So we just collected more and more complete data
そこで私たちはさらに完全なデータを収集しました
Of course we also collected some
もちろん私たちも集めました
Transnational facebook information
国境を越えたフェイスブック情報
just indeed
まさに本当に
Operate as a commercial company
営利企業として運営する
It does require some user use
ユーザーによる使用が必要です
So we're balancing this thing
それで私たちはこれのバランスを取っているのです
good
良い
That's exactly what it's doing
まさにそれがやっていることです
Develop Parchong software
パルチョン ソフトウェアの開発
then collect data
それからデータを収集します
Then build a visual interface
次に、ビジュアルインターフェイスを構築します
I'm sure you're all using Google
皆さんもGoogleを使っていると思います
So what Google gives you is its guess
つまり、Google が提供するのは推測です
You may be interested in these pages
これらのページに興味があるかもしれません
do you charge a key
キーを充電しますか
There is a need, and what I want to know
ニーズがある、知りたいこと
so it recommends
それでお勧めします
EatLocku webpage for you
あなたのための EatLock ウェブページ
then our side
それから私たちの側
Even Google it does something like
Googleでも次のようなことをします
how to say
どのように言って
It guesses you might take the A word
あなたは「A」という言葉を受け入れるかもしれないと思います
But it speculates that the B word is also related to the A word
しかし、B という単語も A という単語に関連していると推測されます。
So it might put the word B in some pages that contain
したがって、以下を含むいくつかのページに単語 B が挿入される可能性があります。
push you like this
あなたをこのように押します
Our main service here is organizations or brands, which are related to business
ここでの主なサービスは、ビジネスに関連する組織またはブランドです。
Or maybe the operator of the cognitive warfare just mentioned
あるいは、先ほど述べた認知戦争のオペレーターかもしれません。
in this way
この上
That means they may need more precise information
つまり、より正確な情報が必要になる可能性があります
For example, today I may be President Tsai Ing-wen
たとえば、今日私は蔡英文総統かもしれません。
then he has many aliases
彼にはたくさんの別名がある
Then I will call up one by one
それでは一人ずつ電話してみます
Then go collect these posts that contain these keywords
次に、これらのキーワードを含む投稿を収集します。
I can't use a blur to show the user something like this
このようなものをユーザーに表示するためにぼかしを使用することはできません
So we actually developed a visual interface
そこで実際にビジュアルインターフェイスを開発しました
Then the difference between him and Google is that
それでは、彼と Google の違いは次のとおりです。
he is pictorial
彼は絵に描いたような人です
He can tell you some comparisons
彼はいくつかの比較を教えてくれる
So what are some of the more influential posts?
では、より影響力のある投稿にはどのようなものがあるのでしょうか?
Then I will show you some pictures later
それでは後ほど写真をお見せしますね
Of course, it is for the fact that I just came here before
もちろん、さっき来たばかりだからです
I was listening to another professor's speech
私は別の教授の講演を聞いていました
He is a professor at National Taiwan University
彼は国立台湾大学の教授です
Then he said that AI is very popular now
そして彼は、今AIがとても普及していると言いました。
Then AI is actually like our children
AIは実際には私たちの子供のようなものです
Maybe when I was studying
たぶん勉強してた頃
Do you need to turn the pages to look up the dictionary?
辞書を引くのにページをめくる必要がありますか?
then progress to
次に進みます
Hey, maybe an invincible translator
ねえ、無敵の翻訳者かもしれない
From now on, mobile phone can check anytime
これからは携帯でいつでもチェックできるようになります
In fact, information is now very easy to obtain.
実際、今では情報は非常に簡単に入手できるようになりました。
Rather, it is whether everyone's analytical ability has kept up
むしろ全員の分析力が追いついているかどうかです
that or
それか
Hey, in fact, some AI is being trained now
ねえ、実は今、いくつかのAIが訓練されているんだ
it can be
かもね
put some mature analysis
成熟した分析を加える
logical or path can turn it into a
論理またはパスに変換できます。
Common people can also use it like this
一般の人もこんな使い方ができる
is that it may use a simple interface for everyone to use
それは、誰もが使用できるシンプルなインターフェースを使用できることです
that's just saying in
それはただ言っているだけです
Well
良い
The so-called cognitive warfare
いわゆる認知戦争
In fact, it is still difficult
実はまだ難しいんです
just have one
一つだけ持っててください
Relatively fixed analysis logic
比較的固定された分析ロジック
because sometimes
なぜなら時々
Uh, the speaker or the party who tried out the message
えー、メッセージを試した発言者または当事者
what is its position
その位置は何ですか
it may be a variable
それは変数かもしれません
Then it can be done in a very diverse way
そうすれば、非常に多様な方法で行うことができます
So in fact, we address some needs of customers
実際、私たちは顧客のニーズのいくつかに対応しています
for example maybe in
たとえば、おそらく
An analysis of an issue, or a
問題の分析、または
uh yes
ああ、そうだね
Some analysis of business needs
ビジネスニーズの分析
We are still relatively high in human intervention
人間の介入は依然として比較的多いです
So we also provide a consultant service like this
そこで、このようなコンサルタントサービスも提供しています
To help customers do some data induction and analysis
お客様によるデータの導入と分析を支援するため
Our interface just mentioned is like this
先ほど述べたインターフェースは次のようなものです
The one on the left is an interface gradually entered from 2014 to now
左側は2014年から現在まで徐々に入ってきたインターフェースです
It's a search engine like Google
Googleのような検索エンジンです
It's just that the information we searched was all social media forums.
ただ、私たちが検索した情報はすべてソーシャルメディアのフォーラムでした。
Or information such as electronic media
または電子媒体などの情報
then we just visualize it
あとはそれを視覚化するだけです
For example, now there is volume
たとえば、今はボリュームがあります
What does the volume mean?
ボリュームってどういう意味ですか？
Because before the community came out, the definition of volume was the volume of articles
コミュニティが登場する前は、ボリュームの定義は記事のボリュームだったからです
But now the definition of volume should be the volume of attention
しかし今では、ボリュームの定義は注目のボリュームであるべきです
That is, how many people interacted with this Facebook post
つまり、この Facebook 投稿と対話した人の数です。
Indicates how much attention this person has paid to this post
このユーザーがこの投稿にどれだけ注目したかを示します
In the past, electronic media or paper media
従来は電子媒体や紙媒体
In fact, it is difficult for you to know that you may look at the circulation
実際のところ、循環を調べてみてもわかりにくいのです。
You may see that it is online media, it may have public
これはオンライン メディアであるかもしれませんし、公開されているメディアであるかもしれません。
what pageviews
ページビュー数
But have these pageviews been verified
しかし、これらのページビューは確認されていますか
don't know
わかりません
So in fact, it will be difficult for you to know the influence of a content
したがって、コンテンツの影響を知ることは実際には困難です。
But social media is relatively organic.
しかし、ソーシャルメディアは比較的有機的なものです。
That is to say, this post is like refueling, I just said it
つまり、この投稿はエネルギー補給のようなものです、ただそれを言っただけです
just maybe a ukrainian
もしかしたらウクライナ人かもしれない
just shared a post about him in Ukraine
ウクライナで彼に関する投稿をシェアしました
How many people follow
何人がフォローしていますか
We can learn from those numbers organically
私たちはそれらの数字から有機的に学ぶことができます
How many people are paying attention to this matter
この件に注目している人はどれくらいいるでしょうか
Yes, so we are presenting in this way
はい、このような形でご紹介させていただきます
Oh that issue
ああ、その問題
It appears in which pipelines have this topic mentioned
このトピックが言及されているパイプラインが表示されます
Then how many people interacted with the posts mentioning this issue in these channels
次に、これらのチャネルでこの問題に言及した投稿にアクセスした人の数は何人ですか?
We visualize it like this
このように視覚化します
Okay, so here's how we organize our information
さて、情報を整理する方法は次のとおりです
that's really in business
それは本当にビジネスです
Will also do some combat dashboards
いくつかの戦闘ダッシュボードも行う予定です
because maybe it is
たぶんそうだから
Whether it is a commercial brand
商用ブランドかどうか
or say a candidate
または候補者と言う
it also says the same
それも同じことを言います
Hey, I'm in every channel
ねえ、私はすべてのチャンネルにいるよ
How many people interacted with
何人と交流したのか
It is presented with a combat dashboard
戦闘ダッシュボードが表示されます
That way it will be quick
そうすれば早くなりますよ
I know what state I'm in now
自分が今どのような状態にいるのかを知っている
Then which direction should I work hard
じゃあどっちの方向に頑張ればいいのか
Or who is kinder to me
それとも私に優しいのは誰ですか
Who is less friendly to me
私にあまり友好的でない人は誰ですか
I can use this way
このように使えます
comparison at a glance
一目でわかる比較
Then of course we also take these things apart
もちろん、これらも分解します
That is, it can also be combined with different
つまり、異なるものと組み合わせることもできます
in internal system
内部システムで
Then or directly use the API to connect with others
その後、または API を直接使用して他のユーザーと接続します
Okay, that's about the end of my company introduction.
さて、会社紹介はこれで終わりです。
I'm just more relevant today
今日はもっと関連性があるよ
still continue
まだ続く
Anyway, everyone may understand the election campaign better.
いずれにせよ、皆さんは選挙戦についてよりよく理解できるかもしれません。
so leave
だから去ってください
so many legislators
とてもたくさんの議員が
In fact, there are many legislators
実は国会議員もたくさんいる
that everyone uses social media
誰もがソーシャルメディアを使用していること
In fact, now using the political capacity of social media
実際、現在はソーシャルメディアの政治的能力を利用しています。
Very almost like maybe 90% 100%
おそらく 90% 100% に近いです
Then they actually sent a lot of questions.
その後、実際にたくさんの質問が送られてきました。
But you and I believe not everyone
でもあなたも私も誰もが信じているわけではない
Every article is tracked
すべての記事が追跡されます
Yes, these legislators are dealing with
はい、これらの議員は問題に取り組んでいます
Everyone is digesting everyone's tax budget
誰もがみんなの税金予算を消化している
Then go to deal with the affairs of the country
それから国政に取り組む
yeah that's just saying
そう、それはただ言っているだけです
time you might normally live
あなたが通常生きているかもしれない時間
you will not
あなたはしません
uh spent so much time chasing down say
ああ、言うことを追跡するのに非常に多くの時間を費やしました
Hey, are these people doing something good?
ねえ、この人たちは何か良いことをしているのですか？
That may be what everyone expected in the past to say
昔は誰もがこう言うと予想していたのかもしれない
We use uh some citizen media to track these people
私たちはこれらの人々を追跡するためにいくつかの市民メディアを利用しています
Are you doing well?
仕事はうまくいきましたか？
But now it's true that citizen media himself demands survival
しかし今、市民メディア自身が存続を求めているのは事実だ
That is to say, he also wants to have a commercial hidden pregnancy.
つまり、商業的な隠れ妊娠も望んでいるということだ。
So I, I would think that actually after social media came out,
それで私は、実際にソーシャルメディアが登場した後、次のように考えています。
Uh, the media industry has changed from being very centralized to a very decentralized structure
ええと、メディア業界は非常に集中的な構造から非常に分散的な構造に変化しました
That's why we're here today to discuss this
それが、私たちが今日このことについて議論するためにここに来た理由です
The problem is that in the past, the ability of the media to try may not have been that important
問題は、これまでメディアが努力する能力はそれほど重要ではなかったかもしれないということです
Because you can't change the structure of that media
そのメディアの構造を変えることはできないからです
But now the power of the media is important because now who
しかし、今ではメディアの力が重要です。
Once a message comes out, everyone may go crazy or something.
メッセージが出たら、みんなが発狂したり何かするかもしれません。
then you need to understand
それなら理解する必要がある
Hey, what is the purpose of this message?
ねえ、このメッセージの目的は何ですか?
how could he affect me like this
彼はどうして私にこんな影響を与えることができたのでしょうか
Yes, the words here mean uh
はい、ここでの単語はえーという意味です
you read so much information
たくさんの情報を読んでいますね
Then who will subtract and sum the information?
では、誰がその情報を引き算したり合計したりするのでしょうか？
Then what impact does he have on society?
では、彼は社会にどのような影響を与えているのでしょうか？
certainly
そうです
As the previous two mentioned, it means different roles
前の 2 つで述べたように、異なる役割を意味します
We can play our respective positions in this social structure
この社会構造の中で私たちはそれぞれの立場を発揮できる
and do these things well
それからこれらのことをうまくやってください
For example, there are indeed some
たとえば、確かにいくつかありますが、
We regularly collate this information
私たちはこの情報を定期的に照合します
and make it available to everyone
そしてそれを誰もが利用できるようにする
Or make some observations about possible legislators
または、立法者候補についていくつかの観察をしてください
Then what about these legislators?
では、この議員たちはどうなるのでしょうか？
This topic will be mentioned differently
このトピックについては別の方法で言及します
Which issues are actually getting more attention from the public?
実際に一般の人々の注目を集めているのはどの問題でしょうか?
Then we are through the classification and labeling of these posts
次に、これらの投稿の分類とラベル付けを行います。
and then take the influence of these so-called post interactions
そして、これらのいわゆるポストインタラクションの影響を受けます
do a calculation
計算をする
After that, it ran out of a chart like this
その後はこんな感じのチャートでなくなりました
Let everyone go for reference
皆さんも参考にしてみてください
Of course, part of the legislator's purpose is to meet some expectations of the voters.
もちろん、議員の目的の一部は有権者の期待に応えることだ。
Then of course he has to meet the party's expectations.
もちろん、彼は党の期待に応えなければなりません。
Or maybe it's on his own personal will
あるいは彼自身の個人的な意志によるものかもしれない
to do a balance like this
こうやってバランスをとります
So we can go this way
だから私たちはこの道を進むことができます
Assist in calibration
協助校正
Some expectations that people have about potentially different objects
人々が潜在的に異なるオブジェクトに対して抱く期待
and then go so that they can optimize themselves like this
そして、このように自分自身を最適化できるように進みます
yes that looks like you
はい、あなたに似ています
Issues of particular concern to the opposition and ruling parties
野党と与党が特に懸念する問題
The issues he used to fight may be different
彼がかつて戦ってきた問題は違うかもしれない。
or his voters
または彼の有権者
his district voters
彼の地区の有権者
In other words, the degree of attention of his supporters is not the same.
つまり、支持者の注目度が違うということだ。
That's how we grab these articles
このようにして記事を取得します
Then there are a lot of them, maybe tens of thousands
それからそれらはたくさんあります、おそらく数万
Then we classify it
それからそれを分類していきます
It should be tens of thousands
何万もあるはずだ
So sort it and go tag it
並べ替えてタグ付けしてみましょう
Then make an analysis chart of influence like this, and it will look like this
次に、このような影響力の分析図を作成すると、次のようになります。
Yes, of course would want to automate this
はい、もちろんこれを自動化したいと考えています
So we also have in the test say
したがって、テストでは次のようになります
Can AI speed up this process?
AI はこのプロセスをスピードアップできるでしょうか?
less involvement
関与が少なくなる
Because we are constructing an analysis logic
分析ロジックを構築しているため
That allows everyone to supervise faster and more efficiently
これにより、誰もがより迅速かつ効率的に監視できるようになります
These are the people who are chosen
選ばれたのはこの人たちです
ok that pair
わかりました、そのペア
These are some of the presentations we made with the data we crawled
これらは、クロールしたデータを使用して作成したプレゼンテーションの一部です
Then everyone can see that
そうすれば誰もがそれを見ることができます
That's actually quite interesting.
それは実に興味深いことです。
for some reason he happens a lot
どういうわけか彼はよく起こります
But his influence may not be that great relatively
しかし、彼の影響力は相対的にはそれほど大きくないかもしれません
probably based on charisma based on the issues he speaks about
おそらく彼が話している問題に基づいたカリスマ性に基づいている
Based on the trust he may have built up with voters in the past or something
彼が過去に有権者と築いた信頼関係か何かに基づいて
will affect the results of these things
これらの結果に影響を与える
He will keep changing dynamically like this
このまま彼はダイナミックに変化し続けるだろう
Yes, so it is true that the information tube is very explosive when there is a lot of information.
はい、確かに、情報がたくさんあるとき、情報管は非常に爆発的になります。
Then we need to have some effective way to organize
それから、組織化するための効果的な方法が必要です
Well, it just so happened that a lot of things like this happened this year.
まあ、今年はたまたまこういう事が多かったです。
Then we have also made some comparative issues for the release of these contents
そして、これらのコンテンツのリリースにあたり、いくつかの比較問題も作成しました
that is to say
つまり
How about the traffic problem on the Internet?
インターネット上のトラフィックの問題はどうですか?
Then how do you pay attention
では、どのように注意を払うのでしょうか？
Did the level of everyone's attention follow the occurrence of some events?
何かの出来事が起こった後、みんなの注目のレベルは上がりましたか?
while rising
立ち上がりながら
Or maybe there are some sub-topics under this big topic
あるいは、この大きなトピックの下にいくつかのサブトピックがあるかもしれません
What are you discussing about those sub-topics?
それらのサブトピックについて何を議論していますか?
What kind of words are mentioned like this
このようにどんな言葉が出てくるのか
Then sort it out in this way so that everyone can understand it better.
次に、誰もがよりよく理解できるように、このように整理します。
Because I believe that when you're dealing with very large
非常に大規模なものを扱うときは、
For example, you may give up reading 10,000 articles
たとえば、10,000 件の記事を読むのを諦めるかもしれません。
But these 10,000 articles seem to be sorted out for you
でも、この 10,000 件の記事はあなたのために整理されているようです
You'll feel like I'm coming to see it like this
こうやって見に来てる気がするよ
That threshold will be much different
その閾値は大きく異なるだろう
that's what we're doing
それが私たちがやっていることです
for citizens like this
このような国民のために
Or maybe some of the media's docking objects like this
あるいは、このようなメディアのドッキング オブジェクトの一部かもしれません
Then you should pile on this cognitive warfare
ならば、この認知戦争を積み重ねるべきだ
It's just that I just mentioned a little earlier
ただ、先ほども少し触れましたが、
That is, we are faced with a large amount of information
つまり、私たちは膨大な量の情報に直面しているのです。
We do some tidying up
整理整頓をします
That part of course tries to automate
もちろんその部分は自動化を試みます
Part of it is still human-involved, and the part looks like this
一部はまだ人間が関与していますが、その部分は次のようになります
then in this state
それからこの状態で
In fact, it also requires the cooperation of many different units of objects
実際には、さまざまなオブジェクト単位の協力も必要です。
that for the government
それは政府にとって
Because in fact, this kind of social platform in Taiwan
というのも、実は台湾にはこの種のソーシャルプラットフォームがあるのです。
mostly foreign
ほとんど外国人
Then I think there are quite a few incidents
それから事件もかなりあると思います
it happens all the time
それはいつも起こります
For example, did you see someone impersonate?
たとえば、誰かがなりすますのを見ましたか?
just a lot
ただたくさん
I show up right after something happens
何かが起こった直後に現れる
Scam syndicates are doing penis comparisons
詐欺シンジケートがペニスの比較を行っている
Immediately there is an impostor etc.
すぐに詐欺師などがいます。
Then he said hey, you can join my LINE group
そしたら彼は「ねえ、私のLINEグループに参加してもいいよ」と言いました。
It's like the stocks are fat and high.
ストックファットハイか何かのようなものです
yes so actually
はい、実際のところ
I think the government is on top of this
政府はこの点を重視していると思う
Need to pay attention to these social platforms
こういったソーシャルプラットフォームには注意が必要です
How to raise possibly some malicious messages
悪意のあるメッセージを生成する方法
The operating threshold looks like this
動作閾値はこんな感じ
For example, how about
たとえば、次はどうでしょうか
Distinguish, compete for position, these things
差別化、ポジション争い、そういうこと
They need to actively discuss with the platform
プラットフォームと積極的に話し合う必要がある
and that is
そしてそれは
Target some influential KOLs
影響力のある一部の KOL をターゲットにする
or influencer
またはインフルエンサー
In fact, he may have been in these people in the past
実際、彼は過去にこれらの人々の中にいたかもしれません
The framework of traditional media to operate
従来型メディアが運営する枠組み
That may be relatively manageable in
それは比較的管理しやすいかもしれません
to a certain extent it won't be
ある程度はそうならないだろう
speak indiscriminately or speak indiscriminately quickly
無差別に話す、または無差別に早口で話す
can be controlled
制御できる
But now because of the platform, everyone can use it freely
でも今はプラットフォームのおかげで誰でも自由に使えるようになりました
then i feel like saying
それなら言いたい気がする
he's like what we usually do
彼は私たちが普段していることと同じです
Disaster drills are the same
防災訓練も同様
These guys have to be more interesting
この人たちはもっと面白くなければなりません
Because he's a man of influence
彼は影響力のある人だから
He must be more interesting to know that he is in this society
彼はこの社会にいることを知るともっと面白いに違いない
What is the role of delivering information
情報を届ける役割とは
Then he has to be more interesting to prevent some
それから、彼は、いくつかのことを防ぐために、もっと面白くなければなりません
The spread of wrong or malicious information
誤った情報や悪意のある情報の拡散
Yes, then I think this is where the government can go
はい、それではここが政府ができるところだと思います
plan some resources and then
いくつかのリソースを計画してから、
Identify influencers on the platform
プラットフォーム上のインフルエンサーを特定する
and then encourage them to participate in something like this
そして、このようなことに参加するよう奨励します
workshop or walkthrough like this
このようなワークショップまたはウォークスルー
Make them more media literate
彼らのメディアリテラシーを高める
Because in fact, for such an influential person
なぜなら、実際、これほど影響力のある人物にとって、
Sure wish he was more media literate.
確かに彼がもっとメディアリテラシーが高ければよかったのに。
Otherwise they do whatever they want
そうでなければ彼らはやりたいことを何でもする
Then the general public will accept it
そうすれば一般の人も受け入れてくれるだろう
Because the content is actually created by a small number of people
実際にコンテンツは少人数で作成されているため、
that most of the people are the ones who receive the content
ほとんどの人がコンテンツを受け取る人であること
Then for these more influential nodes
次に、これらのより影響力のあるノードについては、
Of course there are more things to do
もちろん他にもやるべきことはある
Then again, it is true that the government regularly visits
繰り返しになりますが、政府が定期的に訪問しているのは事実です
Minus and these influential people
マイナスとこれらの影響力のある人々
and then go to the list
そしてリストに行きます
Then also subtract and say they used to pass the comparison
次に、減算して、以前は比較に合格していたと言います
The status of the message in question
問題のメッセージのステータス
what is the extent of the situation
状況はどの程度ですか
Of course we can construct this logic
もちろん、このロジックを構築することもできます
Then do a certain degree of regulation
それからある程度の規制をしてください
I'm not here to talk about regulation
私は規制について話すためにここにいるわけではありません
Not to stop everyone or say
みんなを止めたり言うわけではない
Control people not to speak freely
人々が自由に発言できないように制御する
but that you remind him
でもあなたが彼に思い出させてくれることを
something is wrong
何かが間違っている
then you may want to train him
それなら彼を訓練してみるといいかもしれません
to correct or say
訂正したり言うこと
train him
訓練他
probably try not to have something like this happen
おそらくこのようなことが起こらないように努めているでしょう
the media and influencers
メディアとインフルエンサー
Indeed, he just became
確かに、彼はたった今、
Create some messages and produce and disseminate
いくつかのメッセージを作成し、作成して広める
check mechanism
チェック機構
Right now there are a lot of PR crises like now
今、このようなPR危機がたくさんあります
it happened to some famous people
それは何人かの有名人に起こりました
Then why is this situation?
では、なぜこのような状況になっているのでしょうか？
Because in the past they faced traditional media
過去に彼らは伝統的なメディアに直面していたからです
That node is relatively simple
そのノードは比較的単純です
but now you are
でも今あなたは
After posting a lot of things online
たくさんのことをネットに投稿した後、
I can't get it back
取り戻せない
Then he started spreading out
それから彼は広がり始めました
So actually a lot of people are on it
実際に多くの人が参加しています
unconscious
無意識
He will feel that I can say whatever I want to say
彼は言い​​たいことは何でも言えると感じるだろう
Is it a free society?
それは自由な社会ですか？
Then he didn't expect to say
それから彼はこう言うとは予想していなかった
because it was caused after he sent it out
それは彼が送った後に起こったことだから
how big is this
これはどのくらいの大きさですか
So it's actually suspicious.
ですから実際には疑わしいのです。
that is
あれは
people in the media industry or
メディア業界の人とか、
he is influential
彼は影響力があります
he has to be more conscious
彼はもっと意識的にならなければいけない
Facing the matter of being influential
影響力を持つという問題に直面する
Then he needs to know more about his message
それから彼は自分のメッセージについてもっと知る必要があります
some checks and controls
いくつかのチェックとコントロール
What is the mechanism of self-correction?
自己修正のメカニズムは何ですか?
For some dissemination of news from time to time
随時ニュースを配信するため
how to face
どのように直面するか
Well, he actually has a little
まあ、彼は実際には少し持っています
Public relations image training?
広報のイメージトレーニング？
Then establish some cooperation mechanism with the government platform
その後、政府プラットフォームとの協力メカニズムを確立する
Because in fact these large nodes
なぜなら、実際にはこれらの大きなノードは
It is also easy to receive messages from various parties
さまざまな相手からのメッセージも簡単に受信できます
Do you want to report these messages?
これらのメッセージを報告しますか?
Or should we assist in joint governance?
それとも共同統治を支援すべきでしょうか？
Maybe something is wrong on the platform
プラットフォームで何か問題が発生している可能性があります
to co-govern or something
共同統治か何かに
I think this can be actively discussed like this
このように積極的に議論してもいいと思います
What about the general public?
一般の人はどうですか？
Of course, there are not many tools available.
もちろん、利用できるツールはそれほど多くありません。
Because in fact these platforms
なぜなら、実際にはこれらのプラットフォームは
Of course he's in free mode
もちろんフリーモードです
That is to use everyone to make money.
それは、みんなを利用してお金を稼ぐということです。
So in fact, I think the general public
ですから実際のところ、一般の人は、
to face is
直面することは
How to develop the ability to try
挑戦する力を養う方法
Then I divide it into two categories
それからそれを2つのカテゴリーに分けます
Divided into two categories
2つのカテゴリーに分けられる
Some of them are practitioners like us or
彼らの中には私たちのような実践者や、
Familiar with numbers
数字に詳しい
He has digital ability and digital sensitivity.
彼はデジタル能力とデジタル感性を持っています。
What about this kind of person?
こういう人はどうでしょうか？
is relatively speaking
相対的に言えば
Doesn't need a lot of training
多くのトレーニングは必要ありません
But actually we
しかし、実際には私たちは
That is, the population structure has become an inverted triangle
つまり人口構造が逆三角形になっている
I think the statistical results
統計結果だと思います
In fact, most elders are relatively
実際、ほとんどの高齢者は比較的、
Those who are not familiar with these digital environments
こういったデジタル環境に慣れていない方
Yes, I didn't want
はい、望んでいませんでした
means discrimination
差別を意味します
But this is the result of statistics
でもこれは統計上の結果です
is that you can see that it is
それがわかるということです
If you continue to report a lot, you will be deceived like this.
たくさん報道し続けていると、こうやって騙されてしまいます。
In fact, I think it has something to do with finances and some personal perceptions.
実際、それは財政と個人的な認識に関係があると思います。
So actually I would say
それで実際に私はこう言います
Do your parents take care of themselves?
あなたの両親は自分のことを大事にしていますか？
Or maybe my relatives and friends take care of themselves
それとも親戚や友人が自分のことは自分でやってくれるのかもしれない
that or
それか
Maybe the government or related units can use these resources
おそらく政府または関連部門がこれらのリソースを使用できるでしょう
Education that popularizes these digital literacy
このデジタルリテラシーを普及させる教育
help everyone to identify
誰もが識別できるようにする
that this
これは
Background tea box for some influential objects
いくつかの影響力のあるオブジェクトの背景のティーボックス
that is
あれは
then a message today
それから今日のメッセージ
Then you can first see who the speaker is
そうすれば、まず発言者が誰であるかを確認できます
is he an imposter
彼は詐欺師ですか
Or what purpose does he have?
あるいは彼にはどんな目的があるのでしょうか？
What
何
just make it a habit
ただそれを習慣にしてください
I give an example
例を挙げます
In fact, like in the past, Facebook targeted every fan industry
実際、過去と同様に、Facebook はあらゆるファン業界をターゲットにしていました
he didn't offer
彼は申し出なかった
so-called transparency
いわゆる透明感
information field like this
このような情報フィールド
But after some election turmoil
しかし、選挙の混乱の後、
Has the fan industry changed its name?
ファン業界は名前を変えましたか？
Which area is his manager from?
彼のマネージャーはどの地域の出身ですか?
can be directly compared to transparent
透明と直接比較できます
then i think
それから私は思います
But what he did
しかし、彼がしたことは
Not everyone has this habit
誰もがこの習慣を持っているわけではありません
to check this thing
このことを確認するために
So many people still see
まだ見てる人がたくさんいるから
this person posted
この人が投稿した
heard of this person
この人のことを聞いた
I believe what he wrote
私は彼が書いたことを信じます
it will still happen
それはまだ起こります
That's people with poor digital sensitivity.
それはデジタル感度が低い人々です。
that kind of person
そういう人
We can only remind him
私たちができるのは彼に思い出させることだけです
Train him to raise awareness like this
このように意識を高めるように彼を訓練します
Then I think this is something the general public can do.
それなら、これは一般の人でもできることだと思います。
He has less tools
彼は道具が少ない
because
なぜなら
The analysis tool department also has to learn the threshold like this
分析ツール部門もこのような閾値を学習する必要があります
right good
そうですね、良いです
In the past, the role of the media was indeed
かつてメディアの役割は確かに
Maybe help with vacation?
もしかしたら休暇の手伝いをしてくれるかも？
That is they have something like this reporter
つまり、彼らはこの記者のようなものを持っています
He just went to see how to spread some malicious messages.
彼は、悪意のあるメッセージを広める方法を確認しに行っただけです。
And what is his impact on society?
そして彼は社会にどのような影響を与えているのでしょうか？
then what are those sources
ではそれらの情報源は何ですか
That is indeed a comparison
それは確かに比較です
The so-called intelligence officer looks at the dissemination of these messages from a more overlooked perspective.
いわゆる諜報員は、より見落とされている観点から、これらのメッセージの拡散を観察します。
but you as a facebook user
しかしあなたはFacebookユーザーです
You just take the message and you believe it
あなたはただメッセージを受け取り、それを信じるだけです
that for this kind of person
それはこういう人にとっては
What about this kind of people?
このような人たちはどうでしょうか？
People with low digital sensitivity
デジタル感度が低い人
Of course we can only remind him and train him.
もちろん、私たちができるのは彼に思い出させて訓練することだけです。
like me may be more mandatory
私のように、もっと必須かもしれません
It is possible that my mother passed on some
母から何かが遺伝した可能性もある
I think it's the source of the content farm
それがコンテンツファームの源だと思う
I just help him block these sources on facebook regularly
私は彼が Facebook でこれらの情報源を定期的にブロックするのを手伝うだけです
It's more mandatory to do this.
これを行うことがより必須です。
Because it costs you too much to train him
彼を訓練するにはお金がかかりすぎるから
You might as well just help him deal with it like this
彼がこのように対処するのを手伝うのもいいかもしれません
Of course, this is how it can cover some
もちろん、これである程度のことはカバーできます
Possibly not a very good quality message
あまり質の高いメッセージではない可能性があります
in this way
この上
that or
それか
You see my friend did encounter this time
私の友人が今回遭遇したのがわかります
chaotic
混沌としました
that is there is a wrong message
つまり、間違ったメッセージがあります
stuffed into one
一つに詰め込まれた
the mouth of the most recent topic
最近の話題の口
The person in question didn't say anything about it.
本人はそれについて何も言いませんでした。
But the victim
しかし被害者は
It may be thought by some netizens that
一部のネチズンはこう考えているかもしれない
Are you lying to me?
私に嘘をついていますか？
Are you really busy?
本当に忙しいですか？
That's true being an influencer
インフルエンサーって本当だよな
It should be my second point
それが私の2番目のポイントになるはずです
That is to say, he can only quickly clarify
つまり、彼はすぐに明確にすることしかできません
and use some good
そして良いものを使ってください
Compared with the low-threshold method
低閾値法との比較
Let everyone quickly understand
みんなに早く理解してもらいましょう
Then why am I not what you say
では、なぜ私はあなたの言うとおりではないのでしょうか
or as you know
またはご存知のように
then i think it's a celebrity
それなら有名人だと思うよ
or influential nodes
または影響力のあるノード
some training like this
こんなトレーニングも
Then or you look at ancient times
それから古代を見てみると
also in this wave
この波でも
Let everyone pay attention to this matter
みんなもこの件に気をつけてね
Said that Facebook in Taiwan is in charge of advertising
台湾のFacebookが広告を担当しているとのこと
But
しかし
Why are they still unable to manage efficiently?
なぜ彼らは依然として効率的に管理できないのでしょうか?
Is there still some room for optimization?
まだ最適化の余地はありますか?
I think he is proposing this topic
彼がこの話題を提案していると思う
Make it possible for the government and possibly related units to understand
政府および場合によっては関連部門が理解できるようにする
is it possible to sit here
ここに座ることはできますか
raise the bar higher
バーをもっと高く上げる
Let these scams not be so easy to operate on this
このような詐欺行為が簡単に行われないようにしましょう
And then the digital citizen paragon is what I just mentioned
そして、デジタル市民の模範は、先ほど述べたものです
That is to say, it may be aimed at those with weaker digital skills.
つまり、デジタルスキルが弱い人を対象としている可能性があります。
Of course, there are some open source or relatively low-threshold tools now
もちろん、現在ではオープンソースまたは比較的敷居の低いツールもいくつかあります。
A robot like Meiyu Yiya or something real or fake
Meiyu Yiya のようなロボット、または本物か偽物
can help our friends and relatives discern what Bush's news looks like
私たちの友人や親戚がブッシュのニュースがどのようなものかを識別するのに役立ちます
Then I think what I just mentioned is to preach to them.
そうすると、今私が申し上げたのは、彼らに説教するということだと思います。
Are you checking by example?
例によって確認していますか？
what can you see
なにが見えますか
Messages like this scam usually mean that the benefits are huge
この詐欺のようなメッセージは、通常、利益が非常に大きいことを意味します
Then turn easily
それから簡単に回転します
Then I ask you to join the LINE group that we can't monitor
それでは、監視できないLINEグループに参加していただきますようお願いいたします
what happened there
そこで何が起こった
you have no way of knowing
あなたには知る方法がありません
Then maybe these people were all raised and beaten.
そうすると、もしかしたらこの人たちは皆育てられ、殴られたのかもしれない。
Yes, so we actually need to increase our identification.
はい、ですから私たちは実際に識別力を高める必要があります。
how did these behaviors happen
こうした行為はどのようにして起こったのか
Then when you encounter what kind of behavioral logic
では、どのような行動ロジックに出会ったとき、
you need to be more alert
もっと警戒する必要がある
Just like when we were young, we were called by our mother
幼い頃、お母さんに呼ばれたように
like seeing a stranger
見知らぬ人を見るような
let's not chat with him casually
彼と気軽におしゃべりしないようにしましょう
don't just follow him
彼に従うだけじゃない
is the same reason
同じ理由です
In turn, we need to make these digital capabilities
次に、これらのデジタル機能を実現する必要があります。
Teach weak people how to deal with these things
弱い人たちにこれらのことに対処する方法を教えてください
except defense
守備を除いて
is our own sense of citizenship
私たち自身の市民権意識です
In other words, the organization's defense is improved.
つまり、組織の防御力が向上します。
Then I think outside
それから私は外で考えます
This is not an attack
これは攻撃ではありません
It is to establish friendly units with foreign countries.
それは外国との友好部隊を設立することです。
or the whole country
あるいは国全体
The whole is a large unit
全体が大きな単位です
unit of the people
人々の単位
How to adjust others externally
他者を外部から調整する方法
to our other countries
私たちの他の国へ
or how citizens of other countries perceive us
または他国の国民が私たちをどのように認識しているか
Of course this thing is a bit PR
もちろんこれはちょっとしたPRです
The technique is like Google Trend, it is also a public thing
この手法はGoogleトレンドのようなもので、公開されているものでもあります
It looks like what I'm showing here is the United States searching for the word Taiwan
ここで示しているのは、米国が台湾という単語を検索しているようです
Which related searches in the past seven days are linked together
過去 7 日間のどの関連検索がリンクされているか
Surely this is what Google counts?
Google はこれを重視しているのでしょうか?
It seems to be some kind of Blinken here
ここはブリンケンの一種のようです
when visiting China
中国に行った時のことです
Taiwan is still using the Taiwan Relations Act or something
台湾は未だに台湾関係法か何かを使っている
To do some interaction between countries like this
このような国と国との交流をするために
Yes, then this thing is cross-body in foreign countries
はい、ではこれは外国ではクロスボディです
Then there is Taiwan #MeToo
それから台湾 #MeToo
What else is there such a word as autonomy what is related to Blinken
ブリンケンに関係する自律という言​​葉が他にあるでしょうか。
Then I think these words mean that everyone already has search intentions.
そうすると、この言葉は、誰もがすでに検索意図を持っていることを意味していると思います。
Of course they will have access to a lot of relevant information
もちろん、多くの関連情報にアクセスできるようになります
that might be on the taiwan side
それは台湾側かもしれない
The unit of the representative's speech may need to regularly check these
代表スピーチのユニットはこれらを定期的にチェックする必要があるかもしれません
What you may be searching for
あなたが探しているもの
and check out what kind of content they might receive
どのようなコンテンツが届くかを確認してください
then go to balance
それからバランスに行きます
Have we been bullied for our position on this?
この問題に関する私たちの立場を理由にいじめられたことがありますか?
Threatened or what?
脅迫されたのか、それとも？
As far as our own true thoughts are concerned
私たち自身の本当の考えに関する限り
express it like this
このように表現します
Let everyone search and see like this
みんなもこうやって検索して見てみましょう
So by creating a link like this
したがって、このようなリンクを作成すると、
and then to clarify or say
それから明確にしたり言うこと
To dialectize the correctness of some information like this
このように一部の情報の正しさを弁証するには
ok what else
わかりました他に何か
is that we want to use the characteristic
特性を利用したいということです
Want to make a friendly connection?
友好的なつながりを作りたいですか?
Then I think this thing is like
それから、これは次のようなものだと思います
Taiwan RUSH can do this
台湾RUSHならこんなこともできる
Because indeed we are doing all kinds of content materials
本当にあらゆる種類のコンテンツ素材をやっていますので、
Let everyone know Taiwan
台湾をみんなに知ってもらいましょう
Know what kind of place Taiwan is
台湾がどんなところなのか知る
Know the characteristics of Taiwan
台湾の特徴を知る
Know what is the most popular place in Taiwan
台湾で最も人気のある場所を知る
In fact, Taiwan has a lot of hidden champions
実は台湾には隠れたチャンピオンがたくさんいる
so much light of taiwan
台湾の光がたくさん
how do we use these things
これらのものをどのように使用しますか
How about connecting with the world?
世界とつながってみてはいかがでしょうか？
I believe refueling is usually
給油は通常だと思います
been working on this thing
このことに取り組んでいます
That's actually
それは実際に
I will give two examples
2つの例を挙げます
One is Gemaran
一つはゲマラン
Is Kavalan the light of Taiwan?
カバランは台湾の光?
because in fact
なぜなら実際には
as long as in the world
この世にある限り
man of what may be the world
この世の何者かの男
almost everyone
ほとんどの人
Hey, Gemaran is very ugly, like this
ねえ、ゲマランはとても醜いです、このように
So actually we can use
したがって、実際に使用できます
everyone's interest in this
みんなの関心はこれにある
Let everyone know better
みんなにもっと知ってもらいましょう
Taiwan is a Prospective Place
台湾は有望な場所です
Why is Gemaran's wine so good?
なぜゲマランのワインはこんなに美味しいのでしょうか？
In fact, I don't think there is any need to ask for an answer.
実際、答えを求める必要はないと思います。
everyone we are
私たちはみんな
Hey, am I disconnected?
ねえ、私は接続されていませんか？
I encountered a network outage, a power outage
ネットワーク障害や停電が発生しました
right
右
Yes, that's the same
はい、それも同じです
That is to say, Gemaran
つまりゲマラン
then we use
それから私たちは使います
likely average citizen
可能一般公民
He didn't really pay much attention to the war either.
彼は戦争についてもあまり関心を持っていませんでした。
but ordinary citizens
しかし一般国民
Interests and hobbies in Gemaran
ゲマランの興味と趣味
Let them know more about Taiwan
台湾についてもっと知ってもらいましょう
Is this a way to establish a connection?
これは接続を確立する方法ですか?
May be love without disease
病気のない愛かもしれない
He loves Gemaran and also loves Taiwan
彼はゲマランが大好きで、台湾も大好きです。
Well, the other one is what I want to say
さて、もう一つ言いたいのは、
Hey, of course Taiwan has another geographical advantage.
もちろん、台湾にはもう一つ地理的な利点があります。
Uh, like I saw a foreigner
ああ、外国人を見たような
He came to Taiwan to pay taxes
彼は税金を納めるために台湾に来た
Then he said why he came to Taiwan to pay taxes
そして、なぜ台湾に税金を納めに来たのかを語った。
It's near Kenting
墾丁の近くです
Then he said that the coral reefs in Taiwan are real
すると彼は、台湾のサンゴ礁は本物だと言いました。
Wonders of the world, wonders like this
世界の不思議、こんな不思議
is considered
考えられている
but well worth it
しかしそれだけの価値は十分にあります
And then he's in some dive master's book
そして彼はダイビングマスターの本にも載っています
when i saw this
これを見たとき
he really every year
彼は本当に毎年
I still come to Taiwan to dive once every few years.
今でも数年に一度は台湾にダイビングに来ています。
Then it's time to see these Cape Corals in Taiwan
台湾でケープコーラルを見る時期が来ました
Then I think that there are actually many such things in Taiwan.
そうすると、台湾にはそういうのが実はたくさんあるんじゃないかと思うんです。
Some features that attract people from all over the world
世界中の人々を魅了するいくつかの機能
then of course we are
それならもちろん私たちはです
Do these things individually
これらのことを個別に行う
For example, the one who loves Malan from Aiwei Vision
たとえば、Aiwei Vision の Malan を愛する人
We target these people to tell them what Taiwan is
私たちはこのような人々をターゲットに台湾とは何かを伝えます。
and then target these divers
そしてこれらのダイバーをターゲットにします
Tell them what Taiwan is
台湾とは何かを教えてください
Why Taiwan is worthy of your love
台湾があなたの愛に値する理由
So if we say that Taiwan is attacked today
つまり、今日台湾が攻撃されたと言えば、
Then change to another government
その後、別の政権に政権交代する
Will you not be able to freely come to Taiwan to dive?
自由に台湾に来てダイビングできなくなるのでしょうか？
even with a little bigger emotional blackmail or something like that
たとえもう少し大きな感情的な脅迫やそのようなものであっても
Of course, this way is to let everyone understand more
もちろん、この方法は、より多くの人に理解してもらうためです
So what kind of existence is Taiwan?
では、台湾とはどのような存在なのでしょうか？
let them go through
彼らを通らせてください
through content they are interested in
興味のあるコンテンツを通じて
Enter Taiwan this this objection
これに反対して台湾に入国してください
Then let them know more about the problems Taiwan is facing now
それから台湾が現在直面している問題についてもっと知ってもらいましょう
Then this question may affect him looking forward to the interests like this
そうすれば、この質問は、このような興味を楽しみにしている彼に影響を与えるかもしれません
We connect with the world monitoring power in this way
私たちはこうして世界の監視勢力とつながります
Ok, so this is my sharing today
さて、今日はこれが私のシェアです
that is
あれは
Well
良い
is also
また〜だ
how to say
どのように言って
Everyone may be figuring it out too.
誰もがそれを理解しているかもしれません。
So let's talk about it together
それでは、一緒にそれについて話しましょう
right
右
This director Cai shares with you
蔡監督はあなたと共有します
Then shall we directly invite the other two sharers first?
それでは、最初に他の 2 人の共有者を直接招待しましょうか。
We also made it to the stage
私たちもステージに上がりました
right
右
then next words
次の言葉
of course we
もちろん私たちも
Well
良い
We have prepared some topics
いくつかのトピックを用意しました
wait a minute i will keep
ちょっと待ってください、保管しておきます
How many people will ask this
これを尋ねる人は何人いるだろうか
this sharer
この共有者
then discuss with you
それからあなたと話し合ってください
After all
結局
In addition to what we just shared
先ほど共有した内容に加えて、
Maybe some answers to some questions
もしかしたら、いくつかの質問に対する答えがあるかも知れません
then let me respond first
それなら私が先に答えさせてください
Just now Director Cai mentioned several computers
たった今、蔡局長が数台のコンピューターについて言及しました。
I think it's actually quite interesting
実際かなり面白いと思うよ
just mentioned
先ほど述べた
noodle
面
like our disaster prevention
私たちの防災のように
we will do drills
私たちは訓練をします
face war
戦争に直面する
then we will do
それなら私たちがやります
this
これ
Hanguang exercise and so on
漢光体操など
But in the face of cognitive warfare
しかし認知戦争に直面して
Actually, we didn't do disaster drills.
実は、防災訓練はやっていませんでした。
It was actually good just now
本当に今は良かった
right
右
So actually I think the clip I just mentioned
実際のところ、私が今言及したクリップは
just thought of saying
今言おうと思った
We just saw a lot of scams
たくさんの詐欺を目撃しました
It's all about cheating on points
それはすべてポイントの不正行為に関するものです
It's all a scam
それはすべて詐欺です
It's okay to cheat
騙しても大丈夫だよ
If today is to lie to us about Taiwan's sovereignty
もし今日、台湾の主権について嘘をつくとしたら
Because we had some discussions before
事前に話し合いもしたので
will go through this discussion on the matter
この問題についてはこの議論を進めます
It is said that it is better to buy Taiwan than to fight Taiwan
台湾と争うより台湾を買った方が良いと言われる
Buying Taiwan is worse than cheating Taiwan
台湾を買うことは台湾を騙すより悪い
Yes, I even think about it by myself
はい、自分でも考えてます
That is to say, are these
つまり、これらは
It can be organized to understand who
誰が誰であるかを理解するために整理することができます
The ability to identify information is relatively weak
情報を識別する能力が比較的弱い
then circle them
それから丸で囲んでください
Then for some Honeypot
それからハニーポットを食べましょう
just keep posting the wrong message
間違ったメッセージを投稿し続けるだけ
and then everyone messed up
そしてみんながめちゃくちゃになった
This is also an attack
これも攻撃だ
right
右
This is actually
これは実際には
And I think this is what I want in the future
そして、これが私が将来望んでいることだと思います
I think it's worth it
それだけの価値はあると思います
Not necessarily that we are on this occasion
必ずしもこの機会に私たちがいるとは限りません
there is a way to solve
解決する方法があります
Because in fact, I think especially Q community works
実際、特に Q コミュニティが機能すると思うからです
For example we can maybe
たとえば、おそらく次のようなことができます
You can get some data reports from some communities
一部のコミュニティからデータレポートを入手できます
look at those who target disinformation
偽情報をターゲットにする人たちを見てください
Maybe you can see some fluctuations in the community
コミュニティ内に変動が見られるかもしれません
But that's probably more like what we call an autopsy report
しかし、それはおそらく解剖報告書と呼ばれるものに近いでしょう
We can look back when it's over
終わったら振り返ることができる
OK, so this is how it happened
はい、こうなりました
But if you avoid it beforehand
でも事前に避けておけば
OK, the purpose of this event today
さて、今日のこのアクティビティの目的は
Okay, so then I figured I'd let everyone come
よし、じゃあみんなに来てもらおうと思った
how many guests
ゲストは何人ですか
is to face the war
戦争に直面することです
Then I think this war contains many forms
それでは、この戦争にはさまざまな形があると思います
Entities really did shoot
実体は本当に撃った
outside of war like cannon
戦争の外では大砲のように
And we are now in a
そして私たちは今、
A State of We Call Gray Threat Hybrid War
灰色の脅威と呼ばれるハイブリッド戦争の状態
As if you could actually say we weren't at war
あたかも実際に私たちは戦争中ではないと言えるかのように
aren't we attacked
私たちは攻撃されていませんか
It doesn't seem to be the case
まったくそうではないようです
we're under some kind of war
私たちはある種の戦争下にある
Then how do we face such disinformation
では、私たちはそのような偽情報にどう立ち向かえばよいのでしょうか
Let's say fake news, fake news
フェイクニュース、フェイクニュースと言いましょう
or Xu A's message
または徐亜さんのメッセージ
how should we face
どのように向き合えばいいのか
what tools do we have to deal with him
彼に対処するために私たちはどんなツールを持っていますか
And if we don't have internet anymore
そしてもしインターネットがなくなったら
What to do when online
オンライン時にやるべきこと
This problem seems a bit big and difficult
この問題は少し大きくて難しいようです
I don't know which one has a way to respond to this with us first
どちらが先にこの件に対応できるか分かりません
Did he just say you that tool
彼は今そのツールについて言いましたか？
Can be used even when there is no Internet
インターネットがない環境でも利用可能
Indeed he can use
確かに彼は使える
But the problem is you're inside it's a closed place
でも問題は、あなたがそこにいるのは閉鎖された場所だということです
he is a closed place
彼は閉鎖的な場所です
you're inside assuming you're inside
あなたは中にいると仮定して中にいる
you already have a team
あなたはすでにチームを持っています
Then the information in your team will be released there.
すると、チーム内の情報がそこで公開されます。
But that software he is not
しかし、そのソフトウェアは彼ではありません
I don't think this is the use
これは用途ではないと思います
he is the use of a particular person
彼は特定の人物を利用している
I think there may be something to say here
ここで何か言いたいことがあるかもしれないと思う
Everyone is concerned about, for example, the fact that there is no Internet disconnection.
たとえば、インターネットが切断されないという事実は誰もが心配します。
I think especially for people who don't know how to use the Internet
特にインターネットの使い方がわからない人にとっては良いと思います
He will feel that this is a question of zero and one.
彼はこれがゼロか一の問題だと感じるでしょう。
You used it well today
今日も上手に使いましたね
And no internet means I can't access anything
インターネットがないということは、何もアクセスできないということです
It's not like that
そんなことはないよ
Like we have learned online for a long time
私たちは長い間オンラインで学んできたように
The web is a very complex structure
ウェブは非常に複雑な構造です
let's say
まあ言ってみれば
you said there is no internet
あなたはインターネットがないと言いました
It's because you, let's say your home internet doesn't work.
それは、たとえば自宅のインターネットが機能しないためです。
Or your mobile phone network is not available
または、携帯電話ネットワークが利用できない
Then you probably have the satellite network still on.
その場合、衛星ネットワークがまだ接続されている可能性があります。
Or your radio is still there
あるいはあなたのラジオはまだそこにあります
Or let's say the so-called internet blows up
あるいは、いわゆるインターネットが爆発したとしましょう。
For example, suppose he has a way to cut off your country's external Internet access
たとえば、彼があなたの国の外部インターネットアクセスを遮断する方法を持っていると仮定します。
But your domestic network is good
しかし、国内ネットワークは良好です
For example, if you feed Hsinchu people
たとえば、新竹の人たちに食事を与えるとします。
Then you blow up a communication center in Hsinchu
それから新竹の通信センターを爆破する
then the other you are good
それならもう一方はあなたが良いです
And then and and this kind of stuff he's usually in
そして、そして、そして、彼はいつもこのようなことをしています
after you hang him up
彼を吊るした後
He'll be back in a few hours or a day or two
彼は数時間か1日か2日以内に戻ってくるでしょう
So he hangs up on the Internet, everyone, don't think about it
それで彼はインターネットを切る、誰もそれについて考えない
Wow, once it hangs up, it's all gone
うわー、電話が切れたら、すべてが終わってしまいます
no no no usually
いやいやいや、普通は
Usually in a proven environment
通常は実績のある環境で
He breaks all of a sudden
彼は突然壊れる
or break something in an area
またはその地域で何かを壊す
So everyone, don't use zeros and ones to express this matter.
だから皆さん、この件を表現するのに0と1を使わないでください。
Even if Ukraine is fine, the war situation in Ukraine is very, very critical
たとえウクライナが大丈夫だったとしても、ウクライナの戦況は非常に非常に危機的である
Or when they actually have intermittent internet
または、実際にインターネットが断続的に接続されている場合
after that
その後
Almost everything online is actually good
オンラインのほとんどすべてのものは実際に良いものです
So this might just be a supplement for him.
したがって、これは彼にとって単なる補足である可能性があります。
because I once had to answer a question
かつて質問に答えなければならなかったからだ
I analyzed the whole thing to let people know
人々に知らせるためにすべてを分析しました
The network is a very multi-node and multi-state thing
ネットワークは非常にマルチノードであり、マルチステートです。
It's not that you said that once you hang up, it will be gone.
電話を切ったらなくなると言っているわけではありません。
So everyone may have a correct understanding
だから誰もが正しく理解できるでしょう
I think it's important to have a little mood just mentioned
さっき言ったちょっとした気分も大事だと思う
This is to promote the idea of ​​​​Taiwan Internet
これは台湾インターネットの考えを促進するためです
Did the previous topic talk about it?
前のトピックではそれについて話しましたか？
Our external communication
当社の社外コミュニケーション
Maybe we guide this communication network in Taiwan
おそらく私たちは台湾のこの通信ネットワークをガイドします
Still intact but our external Internet connection may be external Hailan
まだ無傷ですが、外部インターネット接続は外部の Hailan である可能性があります
potentially sabotage so we maybe
潜在的に妨害行為をする可能性があるので、おそらく
I don’t know if my information security information is correct
自分の情報セキュリティ情報が正しいかどうかわからない
Maybe we can't watch Netflix
もしかしたらNetflixが見れないかもしれない
But we can still go to PTT
でもまだPTTには行けるよ
Because TPTT is a network in Taiwan
TPTTは台湾のネットワークなので
But Netflix may introduce foreign servers
しかしNetflixは海外サーバーを導入するかもしれない
Everyone is welcome to watch this Taiwan lecture on health last month.
皆さん、先月の台湾での健康に関するトークをぜひご覧ください
this activity
この活動
There should be videos online
オンラインにビデオがあるはずです
then i think i want it too
それなら私も欲しいと思う
I want to ask again, if so
もしそうならもう一度聞きたいです
Because like, especially otherwise, it means diplomatic marriage or Q club
なぜなら、特にそれ以外の場合、それは外交結婚やQクラブを意味するからです
What's the use of the community
コミュニティの用途は何ですか
just mentioned now
今言ったばかり
major online communities
主要なオンラインコミュニティ
In fact, it is an international platform
実際、それは国際的なプラットフォームです
Really if we meet and say yes
本当に会ってYESと言えば
Taiwan has us
台湾には私たちがいる
maybe intranet
たぶんイントラネット
When the network in Taiwan's own island is still available
台湾本島のネットワークがまだ利用可能な場合
Then if you encounter the external contact section
次に、外部連絡先セクションに遭遇した場合
do we have any other way
他に方法はありますか
Or do we have any method in advance?
それとも事前に何か方法があるのでしょうか？
avoid this from happening
これが起こらないようにする
or even when this happens
あるいはそれが起こったときでも
We can still have a close relationship with the outside world
私たちは依然として外の世界と密接な関係を保つことができます
or enough links
または十分なリンク
Let us call for help
助けを求めましょう
I don't know if you have some experience or ideas like this
あなたにこのような経験やアイデアがあるかどうかはわかりません
Then I, I, just, just had
それから私は、私は、ちょうど、ちょうど持っていた
The host mentioned the question of what to do if there is no Internet
主催者は、インターネットがない場合はどうすればよいかという質問について言及しました
In fact, now the various communities
実際、今ではさまざまなコミュニティが
In other words, the chief and the others can also use advertisements
つまり、署長らも広告を利用できるということだ
This kind of community-based broadcasting could be an alternative when the internet goes down
この種のコミュニティベースの放送は、インターネットがダウンした場合の代替手段となる可能性があります
And radio is also broadcasting is also a practice
そしてラジオも放送ですし練習でもあります
That said, now I know there are other teams working on the kind of mobile that can
そうは言っても、今では他のチームがこのようなモバイルの開発に取り組んでいることが分かりました。
That is, one that can maintain a short-cast communication within a few kilometers.
つまり、数キロメートル以内の近距離通信を維持できるものです。
a machine like this
このような機械
For the short broadcast communication, you can actually buy the transmitter on Shopee
短い同報通信の場合、実際にShopeeで送信機を購入できます
If he is interested, he can buy it and play with it himself.
興味があれば、買って自分で遊ぶこともできます。
And actually before the discussion of disconnection
そして実際には、切断について議論する前に
Everyone, we would like to bring you to discuss the communication network in case of emergency.
皆さん、緊急時の通信ネットワークについて話し合っていきたいと思います。
Or does the network of contacts need to be established first
それとも最初に連絡先ネットワークを確立する必要がありますか?
whether domestic or foreign
国内でも海外でも
It is under a situation, whether it is a natural disaster or a war
自然災害であろうと戦争であろうと、状況下にある
Did your emergency contact person first anticipate who it is?
あなたの緊急連絡先が誰であるかを最初に予想していましたか?
Or you as a government unit
あるいは政府機関としてのあなた
Or you are an information dissemination unit
または、あなたは情報発信部隊です
Do you maintain a good relationship with foreign countries?
外国と良好な関係を維持していますか？
when your country is in crisis
あなたの国が危機に陥ったとき
Is there any way for units in other countries to take you to make an information report?
他国の部隊があなたを情報報告に連れて行く方法はありますか?
dissemination of information or make a retweet
情報の拡散またはリツイート
Because like now, let's say I also work at Radio Central
なぜなら、今と同じように、私もラジオセントラルで働いているとしましょう。
The Central Radio Station and foreign radio stations
中央ラジオ局と外国のラジオ局
is there to maintain a friendly relationship
友好的な関係を維持するためにありますか
Then when one of the media is
次に、メディアの 1 つが
It is when there is no way to continue to spread information
情報を拡散し続ける方法がなくなったとき
Can it be replaced by foreign media?
海外メディアに取って代わられるのか？
that would say something like
それは次のようなことを言うでしょう
Ukraine they have three media companies
ウクライナにはメディア会社が3社ある
Like Oneplus One Media and Starlight Media
Oneplus One Media や Starlight Media のような
That is, they have three media
つまり、メディアが 3 つあるということです。
It is an alliance with United News
United Newsとの提携です
When they were at war, the three media outlets all spoke well.
戦争中、メディア３社はいずれもよく話していた。
If one of them suddenly couldn't broadcast the news
そのうちの 1 つが突然ニュースを放送できなくなった場合
The other two have to make up
残りの二人は仲直りしなければならない
All these communications and coordination must be done before the war
これらすべての連絡と調整は戦前に行われなければなりません
you can't say
言えないよ
I started to fight, I'll come back and think about what I want
戦い始めた、戻ってきて何がしたいのか考えるよ
this might be a bit too slow
少し遅すぎるかもしれません
So in response to the fact that there was no internet just now
それで、今はインターネットがなかったという事実に対応して、
These are the problems of self-communication
これらはセルフコミュニケーションの問題です
In fact, we usually have to put
実際、通常は次のようにする必要があります
Contacts and our partners
連絡先とパートナー
And this information network must first
そして、この情報ネットワークはまず、
Everyone should talk first
まずはみんなで話し合ったほうがいいよ
It's what it's like when you're on alert
警戒している時はこんな感じです
contingency measures
緊急事態対応策
Director
監督
Actually, I think it doesn't matter
実際は関係ないと思うよ
Just to answer this question
この質問に答えるためだけに
Or we're watching him dissect Ukraine
あるいは、私たちは彼がウクライナを解剖しているのを見ている
Some things to do in the face of this war
この戦争に直面してやるべきこと
In fact, there are some examples
実際にいくつかの例があります
I'm still the same as I was in the briefing.
私は説明会のときと同じです。
that is
あれは
It is to use the design method of one seat to one seat to generally improve
全体的に改善するために、1つの座席から1つの座席への設計方法を使用することです。
Everyone for this information
この情報をくださった皆様
There is also the establishment of some collaborative mechanisms for the information network
情報ネットワークのためのいくつかの協力メカニズムの確立もあります。
this matter is very important
この問題はとても重要です
then it needs a drill
それならドリルが必要だ
Let's think about it a little more.
もう少し考えてみましょう。
For example, the exercise just mentioned
たとえば、先ほど述べた演習
Is it just an air defense exercise now?
今はただの防空演習なのか？
Or do we actually have to do more differently
それとも実際にはもっと違うことをする必要があるのでしょうか
Some exercises for different possible situations
考えられるさまざまな状況に対応したいくつかの演習
That or relatively speaking
それか相対的に言えば
Larger of these influential nodes
これらの影響力のあるノードのうち大きいもの
do we need
必要ですか
let them know they are in this
彼らがこの中にいることを知らせてください
possible situation
考えられる状況
what is his role
彼の役割は何ですか
then how will he follow
じゃあ彼はどうやって従うんだろう
Follow his people to do some communication
彼の部下をフォローしてコミュニケーションをとりましょう
Or do some emotional soothing actions?
それとも感情を落ち着かせる何らかの行動をしますか？
Or please support the frontline
もしくは最前線を応援してください
do something like this
このようなことをしてください
That may be through this way
それはこの道を通るかもしれない
Do some information transfer and collaboration between people
人々の間で情報の伝達とコラボレーションを行う
Just now Jiawei also mentioned
たった今、Jiawei さんも言いました
Part of that is about government units
その一部は政府機関に関するものです
between countries
国家間
or those links between the State and other organizations
または国家と他の組織との間のつながり
actually i think
実際私は思う
The usual international network
いつもの国際ネットワーク
or business network
またはビジネスネットワーク
In fact, they are all doing such things
実際、彼らは皆そのようなことをしています
Just for the general public like this
こういう一般向けにだけ
Have we prepared a mechanism
仕組みは用意されていますか
to train everyone
全員を訓練するために
To raise awareness of this matter
この件についての意識を高めるために
I haven't seen it yet
まだ見ていない
but just saw
でも見たばかりです
Digital Diplomacy Association
デジタル外交協会
There are various roles for
色々な役割がありますが、
Start to develop some cooperation mechanisms like this
このような協力メカニズムの開発を開始します
i think its a good start
良いスタートだと思う
That is, I hope everyone can support more
ということで、皆さんももっと応援していただければと思います
also expand it
それも拡張してください
I feel like I am today
今日のような気がする
whether online friends
オンライン友達かどうか
or friends present
または友人が存在する
Everyone can recall
誰でも思い出せる
did you memorize
暗記しましたか
your closest
あなたの一番近い
Phone numbers of family members who live with relatives and friends
親戚や友人と同居している家族の電話番号
Because digital tools are very advanced now
今はデジタルツールが非常に発達しているので、
you now just press
あとは押すだけです
Regardless of Line Messenger
ラインメッセンジャー問わず
Or receive a message according to that image
またはその画像に応じたメッセージを受け取ります
Can you still remember that phone number?
その電話番号をまだ覚えていますか?
good
良い
Looking back on this, I will remind everyone that
これを振り返って皆さんに思い出していただきたいのは、
Do you still remember that there is a way to communicate without the Internet?
インターネットを使わずに通信する方法があることをまだ覚えていますか?
the phone called legacy
レガシーという電話
Telephone lines are different from Internet lines.
電話回線はインターネット回線とは異なります。
So actually
それで実際には
i don't know what to do
何をすればいいのか分かりません
Compared with this age, it is good if everyone still has an impression
この歳と比べて、まだ皆さんに印象に残っていただければ幸いです
Maybe there used to be a time when everyone in the house probably had a landline phone.
もしかしたら、おそらく家の全員が固定電話を持っていた時代があったのかもしれません。
There is a power outage, and the indoor phone can still be played.
停電中ですが、屋内電話はまだ使えます。
right good
そうですね、良いです
You may know this or before
あなたはこれまたはそれ以前に知っているかもしれません
How to use radio
ラジオの使い方
But now everyone still knows how to use radio
しかし今では誰もがラジオの使い方を知っています
So we actually do some
そこで実際にいくつかのことを行います
This one, we have discussed some issues related to the civil affairs before.
これは、民事に関連する問題については以前議論したことがあります。
when researching
研究するとき
There is also an issue to pursue
追求すべき課題もある
Everyone can think about the old public telephone
昔の公衆電話は誰でも思い当たることがある
Compared with the current public telephone
現在の公衆電話と比べて
It used to be more common
昔はもっと一般的だった
Now the public telephones are slowly being dismantled
現在、公衆電話は徐々に解体されています
It's just the coin or the phone card.
硬貨かテレホンカードだけです。
But in fact to some extent
しかし実際にはある程度
It is a temporary reservation
仮予約です
Why?
なぜ？
Those are the few that can stay
それらは留まることができる数少ない人たちです
A Tool for Direct Talk
ダイレクトトークのためのツール
So after going back I think this is a
それで戻ってきた後、これは
take home message
持ち帰りメッセージ
is a national job
国家の仕事だよ
can remember
思い出すことができる
just put it on your back
背中に置くだけ
Do you know the phone number of your loved one
あなたの愛する人の電話番号を知っていますか
what does it look like
それは何に見えますか
right
右
You may just be out of battery
単にバッテリーが切れているだけかもしれません
ok you now see a pay phone
OK、公衆電話が見えました
ok i'm going to call my family
わかった、家族に電話するよ
then you just look at that phone
それからあなたはただその電話を見るだけです
then i don't know what to do
それなら何をすればいいのか分かりません
no above
上記ではありません
you don't know how to contact each other
あなたはお互いに連絡する方法を知りません
Even if the other party's mobile phone can communicate
相手の携帯電話が通信できても
The other party's phone can be reached
相手の電話に連絡できる
but you can't remember
でもあなたは思い出せない
i want acosmetic
化粧品が欲しいです
Like I can't really remember some phone calls right now
今は何回か電話したことをあまり覚えていないみたいです
Subject's phone
対象者の電話
because
なぜなら
It's just that everyone has a mobile phone now, so they can check it directly.
ただ、今は誰もが携帯電話を持っているので、直接確認することができます。
So it's also a possibility
だからそれも可能性あるよ
issues worth discussing
議論する価値のある問題
because
なぜなら
reason
理由
that is
あれは
without these things
これらのものなしで
How do we go when there is no way to inquire
問い合わせる手段がない場合はどうすればよいですか
hit us
私たちを襲う
Contact usWant to contact
お問い合わせお問い合わせしたい
right
右
this is also a key
これも鍵です
I just mentioned that when we are doing research
先ほども言いましたが、研究をしているときに
So found this
それでこれを見つけました
Of course there is another very important point
もちろん、もう一つ非常に重要な点があります
Except your own living relatives and friends
あなた自身の生きている親戚や友人を除く
and your neighbors
そしてあなたの隣人
well maybe you're not where you live
まあ、もしかしたらあなたが住んでいる場所にはいないかもしれません
you want to make sure
確認したいのですか
because something happened
何かが起こったので
Maybe the disaster or the war situation is better
災害や戦況の方が良いかもしれない
You want to settle into the space you live in now
今住んでいる空間に落ち着きたい
is it still suitable to go back or something
まだ戻るのが適切ですか？
do you know your next door neighbor's phone number
あなたの隣の人の電話番号を知っていますか
because our society
なぜなら私たちの社会は
Maybe everyone is crossing back
もしかしたらみんな渡って帰ってるかもしれない
maybe not that friendly
たぶんそこまでフレンドリーではない
so i think it's a good opportunity
だから良い機会だと思う
We actually just actually
私たちは実際にただ実際に
Bowen-Habba or take a few writers to mention that
ボーエン・ハバか、何人かの作家がそれについて言及しています
sometimes you really have to go out and get to know each other
時には本当に外に出てお互いを知る必要がある
know beforehand
事前に知っておく
This is a normal God of War conversion
これは通常のGod of War変換です
We should always be good neighbors and good friends with everyone
私たちは常に誰に対しても良き隣人であり、良き友人であるべきです
Only in time of war can we become each other
戦争の時だけ、私たちはお互いになれる
is a helping partner
助けてくれるパートナーです
get to know them
彼らと知り合う
Then get to know your contact information
次に、連絡先情報を調べます
if there is a need for war
戦争が必要な場合
or in times of disaster
あるいは災害時
that's a way to build closer intimacy
それはより親密な関係を築く方法です
point to point to line
点から点へ線へ
A More Socially Human Approach
より社会的に人間的なアプローチ
This is a bit far
ここは少し遠いです
But I think this is a good place for everyone to go back as homework
しかし、ここは誰もが宿題として戻るのに良い場所だと思います
Then I want to come back and I want to ask you a little more
それからまた戻ってきて、もう少し聞きたいです
Just now I think just now is an important
今だけが大事だと思う
It's a phone number where you can go back and meet people around you.
戻って周りの人々に会うことができる電話番号です。
back it up again
もう一度バックアップしてください
Well, personally, what else can our individual characters do in a war?
さて、個人的には、私たちの個々のキャラクターが戦争中に他に何ができるでしょうか?
But I think some of the examples mentioned earlier
しかし、前に述べた例のいくつかは、
I don't know if there is more I want to share with you, that is
他にあなたと共有したいことがあるのか​​わかりませんが、
It seems that the person seems to be very helpless
その人はとても無力そうに見える
But we found that regardless of experience in Ukraine
しかし、私たちはウクライナでの経験に関係なく、
or experience in other countries
または他の国での経験
In fact, it seems that many people can use different methods
実際には、多くの人がさまざまな方法を使用できるようです
to demonstrate one's own expertise
自分の専門知識を実証するため
Go for defense maybe Ukraine
ウクライナは守備に行くかもしれない
ukraine defense ukraine
ウクライナ防衛 ウクライナ
or Taiwanese professionals
または台湾の専門家
You can use your own profession to defend Taiwan
自分の職業を活かして台湾を守ることができる
I don't know if anyone has more experiences like this
このような経験を他に持っている人がいるかどうかはわかりません
Or share with you what you think you can do
または、自分にできると思うことを共有してください
I think I want to take this opportunity to speak
この機会にお話ししたいと思います
Let's talk about it, I actually started talking about it on the first page
それについて話しましょう、実は最初のページでそれについて話し始めました
In fact, from the very beginning we were afraid and hesitant
実は私たちは最初から怖くて躊躇していました
and then slowly find a way
そしてゆっくりと方法を見つけます
But I think the process
しかし、そのプロセスは、
In fact, most people have
実際、ほとんどの人が持っているのは、
But most of them don't really have a way to figure out how to do it
しかし、彼らのほとんどはそれを行う方法を本当に理解する方法を持っていません
Otherwise, I wouldn't have spent so long looking for it at that time.
そうでなければ、あの時、こんなに長い時間をかけて探すことはなかったでしょう。
But I think this is something to focus on.
しかし、これは注目すべき点だと思います。
That is to say, you are actually giving the public a guideline
つまり、あなたは実際に国民にガイドラインを与えているのです。
what should you do and learn
何をすべきか、何を学べばよいか
Then come to the state of this thing
それからこのことの状態に来てください
Well, this thing is actually a guideline.
まあ、これは実際にはガイドラインです。
that's what you can make you think about
それはあなたに考えさせることができることです
If there are millions of people trying to figure this thing out
このことを理解しようとしている人が何百万人もいるとしたら
what a waste of time it is
なんと時間の無駄だろう
Then if you give it a guideline
それでガイドラインを与えるとしたら
Let's say I start off by saying I've produced a lot of good stuff, right?
まず、私は良いものをたくさん作ったと言うことから始めましょう。
If you see it at first
最初に見たら
Then I don't have to search for these
そうすれば、これらを探す必要がなくなります
I just go straight to the black bear and report something
私はただツキノワグマのところに直行して何かを報告するだけです
you're right into the situation
あなたはまさにその状況に陥っています
i think we might
できると思います
I think often when we discuss these
これらについて議論するときによく思うのですが、
as if we all
まるで私たち全員が
all in one
オールインワン
higher position
より高い位置
For example, what should our government do?
たとえば、私たちの政府は何をすべきでしょうか?
what to do in taiwan
台湾で何をするか
so and so
まだまだ
just bigger
ただ大きいだけ
i think he should
彼はそうすべきだと思う
The left eye is on very, very simple things
左目はとてもとても単純なことを見ています
each of you
皆さんそれぞれ
what can be done
何ができるか
that actually
それは実際に
when each man is exploring what he can do
一人一人が自分に何ができるかを模索するとき
when something needs to be done
何かをする必要があるとき
if there are some guidelines
何かガイドラインがあれば
let him just know
彼に知らせてください
Like I can do this, this, this, this
これ、これ、これ、これができるように
That's actually
それは実際に
those fears or those things
それらの恐怖やそれらのこと
naturally not there
当然そこにはいない
and this thing
そしてこのこと
This is how we learn information
これが私たちが情報を学ぶ方法です
your method is simpler
あなたの方法はもっと簡単です
the more common your stuff
あなたのものが一般的であればあるほど
The more people you reach, the more
より多くの人にリーチすればするほど、
then what we're talking about is
それでは私たちが話しているのは
The cases we are calling for here
こちらで募集している案件は
In fact, most of what can be done is
実際、できることのほとんどは、
People with resources or pipelines and rights
リソース、パイプライン、権利を持つ人々
Then why don't you think about how to make millions of people
それなら何百万人もの人を作る方法を考えてみませんか？
they can both do the same thing
どちらも同じことができます
That power is terrifying
その力は恐ろしいです
it's huge
それは大きいです
To you millions of people want to say
何百万人もの人があなたに言いたいのは
Hey I want to do something for this land
ねえ、この土地のために何かしたい
i gotta get up and do something
起きて何かをしなければならない
Everyone will find his way
誰もが自分の道を見つけるでしょう
Yes, I think it is really to appeal to everyone
はい、本当にみんなにアピールするためだと思います
just find something
ただ何かを見つけてください
can help
助けられる
then go see for yourself
それから自分の目で見に行ってください
Yes, subscribe to send a message every month, anything is actually good
はい、購読して毎月メッセージを送信してください。実際には何でもいいです
as long as you think it's something
それが何かだと思う限り
and most importantly you have to do
そして最も重要なことは、あなたがしなければならないことです
I think this concept is more important
この概念の方が重要だと思います
I think today's audience might be right
今日の聴衆の意見は正しいかもしれないと思う
This topic is of particular interest
このトピックは特に興味深いです
Then if you are from the academic group, you can follow
アカデミックグループの場合は、フォローしてください
Haba and QCircuit
ハバとQCircuit
Those in the Xuewen group can follow me like this
Xuewenグループの人はこのように私をフォローできます
I think it's spreading
広がってると思うよ
Why we keep pushing
私たちがプッシュし続ける理由
Because the threshold for spreading this matter is very low
この件は拡散の敷居が非常に低いので
that is
あれは
Uh, for example, you can practice taking pictures first
ええと、たとえば、最初に写真を撮る練習をすることができます
Practice video starts
練習の録音が始まります
What can I do when I practice taking pictures and practicing videos?
写真を撮ったり、ビデオを練習したりする場合はどうすればよいですか?
It can be used to collect evidence during war
戦時中の証拠収集に使える
Because Ukraine they have a program
ウクライナにはプログラムがあるから
they are
彼らです
Uh, by contacting legal experts
ええと、法律の専門家に連絡して
They are teaching people how
彼らは人々にその方法を教えています
Searching for evidence of Russian atrocities
ロシアの残虐行為の証拠を探す
So you just practice taking pictures and uh, video
だから、写真とビデオを撮る練習をするだけです
This matter is actually
この件、実は
You are a citizen in time of war
あなたは戦時中の国民です
you can play your part
あなたは自分の役割を果たすことができます
that or in normal times
それか平常時
You can go to, uh, look at the ones that are said to be abroad.
海外にあると言われているものを見に行ってください。
What are the channels on social media
ソーシャルメディア上のチャネルとは何ですか
For example, hey, what is Reddy's Taiwanese version doing?
たとえば、ねえ、Reddy の台湾版は何をしているのですか?
go shopping
買い物に行く
Then or say, Hey Reddy's
それから、またはこう言います、ヘイ・レディズ
Uh, Reddy is the American PTT
ああ、レディはアメリカの PTT です
then go and see them
それから行って彼らに会いに行ってください
what is ukraine like on reddy
reddyのウクライナはどんな感じですか？
to explain to foreigners
外国人に説明するために
what happened in your own country
あなたの国で何が起こったのか
They have opened many versions of their own
彼らは独自のバージョンを多数オープンしています
There are actually many on Telegram
Telegramには実際にたくさんあります
uh ukrainian channel
ああ、ウクライナチャンネル
For example, uh Ukrainel or
たとえば、ああウクライナとか
Ukrainel
ウクライナ
Nexta is also a Telegram conduit
Nexta は Telegram のパイプラインでもあります
Anyway, go to other social platforms to tweet more
とにかく、他のソーシャル プラットフォームに移動してもっとツイートしてください
Reddit or Telegram
レディットまたはテレグラム
Take a stroll around these places you are not usually familiar with
普段は馴染みのない場所を散策してみませんか
then you will know
そうすれば分かるでしょう
Okay, so what if something happens today?
さて、今日何か起こったらどうしますか？
I just want to go to these social platforms to transfer information
情報を転送するためにこれらのソーシャル プラットフォームにアクセスしたいだけです
That is usually to record these pipes
これは通常、これらのパイプを記録するためです
Of course, our society usually does this kind of work.
もちろん、私たちの社会では通常、この種の仕事が行われます。
Then the first person in our community will probably
そうすれば、私たちのコミュニティの最初の人はおそらく
Because I just saw an audience ask
ちょうど観客が質問しているのを見たからだ
There are about 400 sponsors this year
今年は約400社のスポンサーが参加
So these 400+ patrons
つまり、これら 400 人以上の常連客は、
we will
私達はします
We want to be a community
私たちはコミュニティになりたいのです
So we now have a Facebook group
それで私たちは今Facebookグループを持っています
Digital Diplomacy Research Office
デジタル外交研究室
Then we start the second half of the year
そして今年も下半期が始まります
regularly in the community
定期的にコミュニティで
To do some network defense for everyone
全員のためにネットワーク防御を行うには
Some topics from the rehearsal will be thrown out
リハーサルの一部のトピックは省略されます
And then there are some Ukrainian ones
それからウクライナのものもあります
feel they do a good job with the site
彼らはこのサイトで良い仕事をしていると感じる
or case
またはケース
We will share with you in the community
コミュニティで皆さんと共有します
So if you are interested in this
それで、これに興味があるなら
then want
それから欲しい
In addition to these 400 people, I also want to come together
この400人に加えて私も集まりたいです
Take this online walkthrough exercise
このオンライン ウォークスルー演習を受講してください
and want to know more about the future
そして未来についてもっと知りたい
That is, if there is some event information in the future
つまり、今後何かイベント情報があれば
You can search for the Digital Diplomacy Lab in the Facebook group
Facebook グループで Digital Diplomacy Lab を検索できます
Then we will do something like this in the second half of the year.
そして、今年の下半期にはこのようなことを行う予定です。
This is how the online drill looks like, thank you
オンライン訓練はこんな感じです、ありがとう
Okay, I think that's just what we're discussing.
わかりました、それが私たちが議論していることだと思います。
So I still have to focus on what I want to express to the government
だから私はまだ政府に何を伝えたいかに集中しなければならない
It is true that, for example, no matter the country
確かに、例えば国を問わず、
It's just an exercise, or the training of the national army.
それは単なる演習、または国軍の訓練です。
I think these things are kind of stuck in the
これらのことはある種行き詰まっていると思います
Maybe a few versions ago
もしかしたら数バージョン前のバージョンかも知れません
Then it actually has a lot of room for optimization
実際には最適化の余地がたくさんあります
Yes, for example, the media is trying to educate
はい、たとえばメディアは啓蒙しようとしています
Is it that the general public has no mandatory self-cognition
一般人には義務的な自己認識がないということか
Or is it actually related to national defense?
それとも実際に国防に関係しているのでしょうか？
That's what we're talking about today, right?
それが今日の話ですよね？
Does this thing need to be a little semi-mandatory?
これは少し半必須にする必要があるでしょうか？
or do you need
それとも必要ですか
Do you need to use some ways to encourage everyone?
全員を励ますために何らかの方法を使う必要がありますか?
To raise awareness and discussion about this stuff
この件についての認識と議論を高めるため
then i think it's
それならそうだと思います
Because I don't know which unit is responsible for this
どの部署が担当しているのか分からないので、
Maybe it's the Department of Books, or the Ministry of Defense.
おそらくそれは書籍省か国防省でしょう。
Anyway, if you really want to do this
とにかく、本当にやりたいのであれば、
In fact, the government can reconsider
実際、政府は再考することができる
how is this thing designed
これはどのように設計されていますか
Then how to let
じゃあどうやってさせるか
Just like what his dad said
彼のお父さんの言う通りだ
get more people involved
より多くの人を巻き込む
Because of course I believe that folk power is very
もちろん民の力​​はとても強いと信じているので、
very powerful
とてもパワフルな
But in fact, if you only look at Taiwanese society
しかし実際、台湾社会だけを見てみると、
It is very difficult to gather consensus
コンセンサスを得るのは非常に難しい
is there something
何かがあるの
probably relatively speaking
おそらく相対的に言えば
That is, the official resources are available to support everyone.
つまり、誰でもサポートできる公式リソースが利用可能です。
Or classify the roles?
それとも役割を分類しますか？
that is of course if
それはもちろんです
I think now some parts
今思うと、いくつかの部分は
may still stay
まだ残るかもしれない
so-called hardware
いわゆるハードウェア
But what we are discussing today is more software-oriented
しかし、私たちが今日議論していることは、よりソフトウェア指向のものです
network of people
人のネットワーク
It's actually soft
実は柔らかいんです
Information dissemination is actually software-oriented
情報発信は実はソフトウェア中心
the training of these things
こういったことの訓練
There are mechanisms
仕組みがあります
The establishment seems to have less pondering in the past
施設側は以前はあまり深く考えていなかったようだ
Is it necessary to spend more time cultivating him in recent years?
近年は育成にもっと時間をかける必要があるのでしょうか？
I think it will be a problem that everyone may have to face in the future.
将来的には誰もが直面しなければならない問題になると思います。
Because of course it's too easy to buy a weapon
もちろん武器を買うのは簡単すぎるから
So buying a weapon is of course an international declaration.
したがって、武器を購入することは、当然のことながら国際宣言です。
But what?
でも何？
that networking we're talking about today
今日私たちが話しているネットワーキングについて
How can it be generally improved
一般的にどうすれば改善できるでしょうか
How can we start an open discussion
オープンなディスカッションを始めるにはどうすればよいですか
conscious discussion
意識的な議論
This is actually what everyone has to face now
これは実際に今誰もが直面しなければならないことです
that can't
それはできない
Ah Fa can't be talking about those of us
Ah Faは私たちのことを話すことはできません
Maybe someone who is already interested is discussing it here
もしかしたらすでに興味を持っている人がここで議論しているかもしれません
but those possibilities
しかしそれらの可能性は
Originally, he might face life just thinking that
本来はそれを感じるためだけに人生と向き合っているのかもしれない
Oh this thing has nothing to do with me
ああ、これは私には関係のないことです
How is he going to get involved in this?
彼はこれにどのように関与するつもりですか？
I think everything can be thought and designed
すべては考えてデザインできると思う
That is
あれは
what i want to say to the government
政府に言いたいこと
because I think it is
そうだと思うから
um yes
ええと、はい
possible
可能
lost something
何かを失った
Like actually I think just now
実際に今思ったように
come meet air defense exercise
防空演習に来てください
I also often ask
私もよく質問します
That's the alarm
それは警報です
Everyone can move, is that all?
みんな動ける、それだけ？
or what are we going to do
それとも何をするつもりですか
I'm a bit confused about the purpose of this exercise
この演習の目的について少し混乱しています
So actually on this
それで実際にこれに関しては
I believe there is much more that can be done
もっとできることはたくさんあると信じています
Director Cai's reminder just now
蔡監督の今のリマインダー
I think it's very heavy
とても重いと思います
this is an important reminder
これは重要な思い出です
Because in fact, we are now in Taiwan
実は私たちは今台湾にいるのです
I don't have to speak for the government first.
まず政府を代弁する必要はない。
That is to say, compared with the past few years, we are now
つまり、ここ数年に比べて、今は
In fact, there is indeed continuous progress
実際、確かに継続的な進歩が見られます
But I think it's also because
でもそれもあるからだと思う
In the process of seeing such progress
そのような進歩を見る過程で
So it will be more tense, that is to say
つまり、より緊張することになります。
why not fast enough
なぜ十分に速くないのか
Why do you still seem to be walking slowly
どうしてまだゆっくり歩いているように見えるの
maybe that's their limit
それが彼らの限界なのかもしれない
The pace of the government may be slower
政府のペースは遅くなるかもしれない
so i think this comes back
だからこれは戻ってくると思う
Today's topic is Xiao Bo Da
今日のテーマは小伯達です
I'm actually thinking about when this little uncle was growing up
私は実際にこの小さな叔父が成長したときのことを考えています
Think about it from another angle
別の角度から考えてみましょう
Not so much small or large to some extent
ある程度小さいか大きいかではない
Kind of like our role today is all bottom up
今日の私たちの役割はすべてボトムアップのようなものです
How to use the power of the people
国民の力をどう活用するか
what do we do
私たちは何をしますか
to bring about change in the government
政府に変化をもたらすために
This is just an example of what we say and do.
これは私たちの言動の一例にすぎません。
In fact, it’s like lying on the grass, we have previously focused on the issue of civil defense
実際、それは草の上に横たわっているようなものです、私たちは以前に民間防衛の問題に焦点を当ててきました
We made a civil defense manual of the original folk version
オリジナル民間版の民間防衛マニュアルを作成しました
after we did
私たちがやった後
The Defense Forces of course also have their version out
もちろん国防軍バージョンも出ています
We're all around 2022
2022 年が近づいています
It came out around the sixth day of the new year
正月6日くらいに出ました
do it
やれ
after comparison
比較後
In 2023, the Ministry of Defense decided to make a new version of the Civil Defense Manual
防衛省は2023年に民間防衛マニュアルの新版を作成することを決定
OK, what does this mean? It means
OK、これはどういう意味ですか?
There is more progress
さらに進歩があります
When the folks made a version
みんながバージョンを作ったとき
The Ministry of National Defense or government departments may read it and say
国防省や政府部門がそれを読んでこう言うかもしれない。
well , he has a reference
そうですね、彼は参考資料を持っています
Even if maybe doing this will work
たとえこれをやればうまくいくかもしれないとしても
He is also more confident that
彼はまた、次のように自信を持っています
I can maybe try this place
この場所を試してみてもいいかもしれません
So including the example that Haba just mentioned before
先ほど羽場さんがおっしゃった例も含めて
They folk our own energy
彼らは私たち自身のエネルギーを集めます
Let's start with a small-scale approach with small resources
少ないリソースで小規模なアプローチから始めましょう
After doing a minimum feasible solution first
最初に実行可能な最小限の解決策を実行した後、
Hey, the police, hey, some policemen are still participating in this event
おい、警察、おい、まだこのイベントに参加している警察官もいる
Hey, I can use it in my official business
ほら、公務でも使えるよ
If it can work, it will be added
動作できれば追加します
or I believe the Society for Mathematical Diplomacy has many
あるいは、数学外交協会には多くの専門家がいると思います。
In fact, the experience of cooperating with the official department
実際に公式部門と協力した経験
will find out that
それが分かるだろう
In fact, many of them are willing to try
実際、彼らの多くは喜んで挑戦します
but they have their burdens
しかし彼らには重荷がある
have their baggage
彼らの荷物を持っています
I dare not jump in like this in one breath.
私はこのように一気に飛び込む勇気はありません。
So this is an obstacle they have
つまり、これは彼らが抱えている障害なのです
It's also very similar to our folks who have to first
それはまた、最初にやらなければならない私たちの人々と非常によく似ています
as a young uncle
若い叔父として
Close first
優先合上
go and show them
行って見せてください
Just say OK we're doing this workable
OKと言ってください、これは実行可能です
can be successful
成功できる
They just jumped in betting resources
彼らは賭けのリソースに飛びついただけです
Then scale this up
次に、これをスケールアップします
but i think this thing
でも私はこのことを思う
In fact, I just thought that this Q-Such major also has something to do with it.
実は、このQ-Such専攻もそれに関係しているのではないかと思ったのです。
I feel as though we can't just put a responsibility like that
そんなに責任を押し付けることはできないような気がする
blame the government
政府を責める
In fact, there is another very important role is
実は、もう一つ非常に重要な役割があります。
The role of these big platforms
これらの大きなプラットフォームの役割
Well, I think we just discussed this thing today
そうですね、今日このことについて話し合ったばかりだと思います
remind me of a theme
テーマを思い出させてください
Because actually I know how many there are in Taiwan now
なぜなら、私は今台湾に何人いるのか知っているからです。
The international big platform is now in
国際的なビッグプラットフォームが登場
Regardless of whether you are practicing or singing, you are studying and saying
練習しても歌っても勉強してるって言ってる。
They seem to be trying to provide a funding
資金を提供しようとしているようだ
Let us, the civil society in Taiwan, offer some projects
私たち台湾の市民社会がいくつかのプロジェクトを提案しましょう
Proposal to do something regardless of the media system
メディアシステムに関係なく何かをやろうという提案
Or related news, compensation and other plans
または関連ニュース、補償、その他の計画
To make Taiwan society better, this digital citizen willful
台湾社会をより良くするために、このデジタル市民は意志を持っています
Maybe I think we just mentioned these projects
たぶん、これらのプロジェクトについて言及したばかりだと思います
These directions are worth following whether it is Google
これらの指示は、Google であっても従う価値があります。
Facebook or some large digital platform
Facebook またはその他の大きなデジタル プラットフォーム
Check out some of their directions for proposals
提案の方向性をいくつか確認してください
Or whether it's the audience in the audience or the friends online
あるいはそれが会場にいる観客であっても、オンライン上の友人であっても
If you have such an idea, you can actually go
そんな思いがあれば実際に行ってみてもいいでしょう
search related information
関連情報を検索する
I think it's a
だと思います
Another change
もう一つの変化
because they are more resilient than the government sector
彼らは政府部門よりも回復力があるからです
There are also resources
リソースもあります
can make some things go faster
いくつかのことをより速く進めることができる
Improve Taiwan's social willfulness
台湾の社会的意欲を改善する
Well, I actually think that the whole scene just now
そうですね、実際のところ、今のシーン全体がそうだと思います
One thing that strikes me as something to give back is to say
恩返しとして私が印象に残っていることの一つは、こう言うことです。
In fact, we generally think that it is the same in the face of war.
実際、私たちは一般に、戦争に直面しても同じだと考えています。
From the very beginning, it seems that
最初からそう思われる
There must be defenses such as tanks, aircraft, missiles, etc.
戦車、航空機、ミサイルなどの防御手段が必要です。
but
しかし
In fact, we just discovered through this field event
実は私たちはこのフィールドイベントを通して初めて知りました
Not really, we have so many ways
そうではありません、方法はたくさんあります
Can improve Taiwan's defense
台湾の防衛を改善できる
improve our defense
私たちの守備を改善する
then we
それから私たち
Uh, before our analogy would be something like
ええと、私たちのたとえが次のようなものになる前に
You can imagine Taiwan's defense
台湾の防衛を想像できる
maybe like a tower of refinement
洗練の塔のようなものかもしれない
if you really wanna get a gun
本当に銃を手に入れたいなら
the one who operates the tank
戦車を操作する人
This operational missile goes to war
この運用可能なミサイルは戦争に突入する
You can go to the very top, the very top of this participation
あなたはこの参加の一番上、一番上に行くことができます
join our army
私たちの軍隊に参加してください
to get involved in the Ministry of Defense
防衛省に関与する
But we also know that it is not
しかし、そうではないことも私たちは知っています
Because in fact, if you want to participate, you want to go to the heavy army, you still have conditions
なぜなら、実際に参加したいなら、重軍に行きたいなら、まだ条件があるからです
How old are you, and what about your physical condition?
あなたは何歳ですか、体調はどうですか？
if you can't
それができないなら
In fact, there are many things to participate in
実は参加できるものがたくさんあるんです
In fact, there are some in various counties and cities
実際にはいくつかありますが、
Uh, the police units are open
ああ、警察は開いています
you can join the community
コミュニティに参加できます
civil defense groups
民間防衛グループ
This may be the police unit, you can authorize relevant information
これは警察部隊である可能性があります。関連情報を許可できます
You can join one of the communities like this
このようなコミュニティのいずれかに参加できます
civil defense team
民間防衛チーム
or
また
Actually, let's take a step back
実際、一歩下がってみましょう
when there is a real war or war
実際の戦争や戦争が起こったとき
you just have to do one thing
あなたはただ一つのことをしなければなりません
you can save yourself
あなたは自分自身を救うことができます
no other trouble
他に問題はありません
Don't need other governments and PhDs to help you
他の政府や博士号の助けは必要ありません
It's already a blessing
それはもう祝福です
If you can save yourself today
今日自分を救えるなら
your family
あなたの家族
your community
あなたのコミュニティ
Then if they can have such a defense
それでこれだけの防御力があれば
Or at least don't need help
あるいは少なくとも助けは必要ない
If you still want to come to Huazhi to help you
それでも華志に来て助けたいなら
If every community has such basic capabilities
すべてのコミュニティがそのような基本的な機能を備えていれば
In fact, we are facing the war we may encounter
実際、私たちは遭遇する可能性のある戦争に直面しています
will be more resistant
より耐性が高くなります
I think it's actually something everyone can do
実は誰にでもできることだと思う
you probably didn't think to say
あなたはおそらく言うつもりはなかったでしょう
It turns out that this incident actually helps our defense.
この事件は実際に私たちの防衛に役立つことが判明しました。
But actually silently
でも実際は黙って
learn more by yourself
自分でもっと学ぶ
learn more over there
あそこでもっと勉強してください
Guo Xiang just mentioned
郭祥氏が先ほど言及した
try yourself, contact yourself
自分自身を試して、自分自身に連絡してください
no matter what you do on the internet
インターネット上で何をしても
Occasionally post articles
たまに記事を投稿します
To establish some contacts with international friends
国際的な友人との連絡を確立するため
Or walk to some physical activities
または、歩いて身体活動をすることもできます
to learn some skills
いくつかのスキルを学ぶために
Or just know someone
あるいは誰かを知っているだけ
In fact, it is unconsciously improving Taiwan's defense against possible wars.
実際、それは潜在的な戦争に対する台湾の防衛力を無意識のうちに向上させている。
Enhance the social humanity of our citizens
国民の社会的人間性を高める
I wonder if there are a few people who haven't added anything today?
今日は何も追加してない人も少ないかな？
OK, thanks
わかりました、ありがとう
add a concept
コンセプトを追加する
In our business world
私たちのビジネスの世界では
Actually, I want this first
実はこれが一番欲しいんです
What I want to express is that this is called risk management
私が言いたいのは、これがリスクマネジメントということです
that is, your risk management
つまり、リスク管理です
If you have a possible risk in the future
将来的にリスクがある可能性がある場合
war is a big risk
戦争は大きなリスクだ
Regardless of the fact that I sometimes
時々あるという事実にもかかわらず、
so-called community
いわゆるコミュニティ
I'm a pauper and I don't risk as much as you rich people
私は貧乏人なので、あなた方の金持ちほどリスクは冒しません
You have a lot of money, you are an entrepreneur, what, what, your risk is much bigger than mine
あなたはたくさんのお金を持っています、あなたは起業家です、何、何、あなたのリスクは私よりもはるかに大きいです
because you have a lot to lose
失うものがたくさんあるから
Then we we are alone, he is equivalent to not early but
それから私たちは一人です、彼は早くないことに相当しますが、
But most importantly he is actually a concept of risk
しかし最も重要なことは、彼は実際にリスクの概念であるということです
then you at your risk
それならあなたは危険を冒してください
You should invest to curb his risk no matter what method you use
どのような方法を使用するとしても、彼のリスクを抑えるために投資する必要があります
to restrain him
彼を拘束するために
If I were an entrepreneur, I would like to invest in these civic communities
もし私が起業家だったら、これらの市民コミュニティに投資したいです
You just give him a little donation, give him a little support
あなたは彼に少しの寄付をして、少しのサポートをするだけです
For him, it is something that can amplify his strength many times
彼にとってそれは自分の力を何倍にも増幅できるもの
Then you invest a little bit
それから少し投資してみます
It is very valuable for your risk control
リスク管理にとって非常に価値があります
Then I take this opportunity to appeal
それではこの機会に控訴させていただきます
In case some of them belong to rich people
そのうちの何人かが富裕層に属している場合
use your money like this
お金をこうやって使う
is the most effective investment
最も効果的な投資です
There are many caring people here
ここには思いやりのある人がたくさんいます
they actually look like that
彼らは実際そのように見えます
Digital Diplomacy Association
デジタル外交協会
In fact, I think they raised hundreds of thousands of funds.
実際、彼らは数十万の資金を集めたと思います。
I actually have a really bad headache
実はかなり頭痛がひどいんです
Something so important to the country has to come out to raise funds
国にとって非常に重要なものは資金を集めるために出なければなりません
Then we got fundraising and only got a few hundred thousand
その後募金活動をしましたが、集まったのは数十万円だけでした
Rich people, think about it yourself
お金持ちの人は自分で考えてください
How do you protect your money?
どうやってお金を守りますか？
Thanks
ありがとう
that event last
最後のあのイベント
I think we should remind everyone
みんなに思い出させるべきだと思う
Attorney General Guo just reminded everyone
郭司法長官が皆さんに思い出させました
To click like, post these various units Q search
「いいね！」をクリックするには、これらのさまざまなユニットを投稿してください Q検索
and Haba or all diplomatic societies
ハバまたはすべての外交協会
There is another very important unit that everyone must forget
誰もが忘れなければならない非常に重要な単位がもう 1 つあります
You can also search for lying tide digging
寝潮掘りも検索できます
Welcome everyone to press like, leave a message, share and subscribe to open the small bell
みなさん、「いいね！」を押し、メッセージを残し、共有し、購読して小さなベルを開くことを歓迎します
Lock our various related reports
さまざまな関連レポートをロックする
In fact, our issue of civil defense
実際、私たちの民間防衛の問題は、
Or especially this issue last month about critical infrastructure
特に重要インフラに関する先月のこの問題
We all have some relevant news stories
誰もがいくつかの関連ニュースを持っています
Is it the last addition?
最後の追加かな？
i want to add
追加したい
Because what we are discussing today has a topic called
なぜなら、私たちが今日議論していることには、次のようなトピックがあるからです。
very confident
非常自信
We discuss these things very confidently
私たちはこれらのことについて非常に自信を持って議論します
Then we need to optimize everyone's awareness and cognition of these things.
次に、これらのことに対する全員の意識と認識を最適化する必要があります。
Of course I think it takes a little bit of self-confidence
もちろん、ある程度の自信は必要だと思いますが、
That is to say that it is a bit like the media leading the way.
つまり、メディアが主導しているようなものです。
It’s just that Taiwanese people like to line up, right?
ただ台湾人は並ぶのが好きなんですよね？
So actually I think it should be broad
だから実際には幅広くあるべきだと思う
Possibly set up some workshops
いくつかのワークショップを開催する可能性があります
or set up some lectures like this
または、このような講義をいくつか設定してください
And maybe use it as a marketing campaign
マーケティング キャンペーンとして使用することもできます
go get these people in
この人たちを迎えに行って
and when these seeds are scattered
そしてこれらの種が散らばるとき
Everyone will know better how to discuss this topic
誰もがこのトピックについて議論する方法をよりよく理解できるようになります
Yes, you see, of course today's lecture is free to attend.
はい、もちろん今日の講義は無料で参加できます。
But are there some
でもいくつかありますか？
so-called network optimization strategy
いわゆるネットワーク最適化戦略
can go and take some people slowly
ゆっくり何人か連れて行ってもいいよ
For the idea of ​​this question, pull it out
この質問のアイデアについては、引き出してください
Then let them be willing to discuss this matter with the people around him
それから、この件について周囲の人々と喜んで話し合ってもらいましょう。
I think it's a big topic too
これも大きな話題だと思います
Of course this matter
もちろんこの件も
He is education, right?
彼は教育ですよね？
So actually I would say
それで実際に私はこう言います
Really, why keep talking to the government?
本当に、なぜ政府と話し続けるのでしょうか？
because I think the government can be on top of this
政府はこの問題を乗り越えられると思うから
do a lot of thinking and do a lot of trying
たくさん考えて、たくさん試してください
that's only possible now
それは今しかできないことだ
I think it's more important
それの方が重要だと思う
What I do must have a performance
私のやることにはパフォーマンスが必要です
But it's hard for him to measure performance
しかし彼にとってパフォーマンスを測定するのは難しい
to him is an education
彼にとっては教育だ
He is just promotional
彼はただの宣伝活動をしているだけだ
So all I can think of is to do more of this.
したがって、私が考えることができるのは、これをもっと行うことだけです。
Then let everyone have such thoughts
じゃあみんなもそんな考えを持ってください
let these seeds disperse more
この種をもっと分散させましょう
Discuss with everyone, inspire with everyone
みんなで議論し、みんなで刺激する
more likely like
おそらく好きです
Like this, people like Dad come out
こうやってお父さんみたいな人が出てくるんだよ
Set a problem by yourself and solve this problem like this
自分で問題を設定し、この問題を次のように解決します
Of course, this kind of toughness is generally improved.
もちろん、この種の靭性は一般的に向上します。
Thank you very much for Director Jiang's supplement
ジャン監督の補足、本当にありがとうございました
Then I believe that today we have a lot of calls to the government
それから今日は政府に対してたくさんの電話があると思います
Taiwan Internet Lecture Hall will post this news recently
台湾インターネット講堂は最近このニュースを掲載します
pass it on to our senior management
それを上級管理職に伝えます
Or in front of the screen, or friends at the scene
あるいはスクリーンの前で、あるいは現場の友人たちで
If it was mentioned just now, like Dad mentioned, people with great resources
先ほどパパが言ったように、素晴らしいリソースを持った人々について言及したとしたら
we have four here
ここには4つあります
you are welcome
どういたしまして
provide resources
提供資源
The risk of war inside the drop plane
降下飛行機内での戦争の危険性
Alright, that's the end of today's activities.
さて、今日の活動はこれで終わりです。
Or do you have anything to add?
それとも何か付け加えることはありますか？
ok i think that's it we will
わかりました、それでいいと思います、そうします
This is the end of today's event, thank you for your participation
本日のイベントはこれで終了です、ご参加いただきありがとうございました
Thank you also for this online
こちらもオンラインでよろしくお願いします
The audience should currently have
視聴者が現在持っている必要があるのは、
I don't remember saying there should be around 70 bits
70ビットくらいあるべきだと言ったことは覚えていない
That
それか
I saw his question, the cheering one just now has an appropriate reply
彼の質問を見た、今応援している人が適切な答えを返した
Then Dad also helped us reply on the message board.
それからお父さんも掲示板に返信するのを手伝ってくれました。
then i think we are today
それから私たちは今日だと思います
This is the end of today's activities
これで今日の活動は終了です
Thanks again to all of our speakers today
本日は講演者の皆様に改めて感謝申し上げます
Then I will also advertise
それでは宣伝もさせていただきます
Our next lecture event
次回の講演会イベント
More interesting topics will be discussed
もっと興味深い話題が議論されるでしょう
The Social Responsibility of Internet Celebrities
インターネット有名人の社会的責任
Then you are welcome to come to us again
それではまたお越しくださいませ
lecture hall
講堂
The lecture hall website is coming up to make a registration
講堂のウェブサイトに登録ができるようになりました
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
Then we have posted in this message area
その後、このメッセージエリアに投稿しました
Satisfaction survey for today's event
本日のイベントの満足度調査
Please also help us to fill in
記入もご協力ください
Then let's buy everyone a cup of coffee
それならみんなにコーヒーを買ってあげましょう
ok thank you all
わかりました、皆さんありがとう
This is the end of today's activities
これで今日の活動は終了です
Thanks
ありがとう
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
you
あなた